[[{"No": 1, "Stem": "In 1996, ____ 805 million Smart cards were issued, with an estimated 2.8 billion to be distributed in 2000.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Applying the engineering feedback concept, we can search and reach the optimum ____ with a very small number of tests.", "Opt_1": "debate", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "condition", "Answer": "condition", "Opt_1_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "state"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some assignments will be graded; others will ____ receive a check-mark.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A large ____ map shows a small area with a large amount of detail.", "Opt_1": "scale", "Opt_2": "decade", "Opt_3": "community", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "scale", "Opt_1_def": "extent", "Opt_2_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many of the students were unable to ____ the relevance of the mathematics they had learned and so could not make use of it.", "Opt_1": "perceive", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "determine", "Opt_4": "isolate", "Answer": "perceive", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_4_def": "to separate something or someone from others"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You will need to request a ____ leave of absence with USC if you intend to be away from more than 3 days.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "forthcoming", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "formal", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "coming soon", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Megan Wood said although students were more educated on the issues, many did not vote ____ because they forgot to request an application form.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "That plan specifies that only the top 12.5 percent of California high school graduates should be considered ____ for UC admission.", "Opt_1": "eligible", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "harsh", "Opt_4": "likely", "Answer": "eligible", "Opt_1_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_4_def": "probable"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I hesitate to put all of my lecture notes online because I do want students to ____ the lectures.", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "spread", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "prosper", "Answer": "attend", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to do well; to become rich"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is our belief that the students were not given a fair hearing, and ____ that the punishment was unjust.", "Opt_1": "moreover", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "hardly", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "furthermore", "Opt_1_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "not very much", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Those who will be attending the event should try to make it to the Speedway early to ____ the rush hour traffic.", "Opt_1": "edit", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "impose", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She is yet to master basic verb grammar. She often says He do .. ____ of He does ...", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Thus, there is no question but that the donor intends this gift to be for the ____ use of Princeton University.", "Opt_1": "vast", "Opt_2": "credible", "Opt_3": "sole", "Opt_4": "poor", "Answer": "sole", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "believable", "Opt_3_def": "only", "Opt_4_def": "bad, unsatisfactory"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "As the number of old people increases, so has the concern that there is not enough money in the health system to take ____ care of them.", "Opt_1": "average", "Opt_2": "typical", "Opt_3": "proper", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_2_def": "usual", "Opt_3_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We used this information to construct a continuous measure of the ____ of subject-specific coursework to total coursework.", "Opt_1": "condition", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "ratio", "Answer": "ratio", "Opt_1_def": "state", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most scientists ____ that the life expectancy of people in developed countries will continue to rise.", "Opt_1": "modify", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "presume", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to believe, assume"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Too much stress can ____ problems with mental and physical health, particularly over a prolonged period of time.", "Opt_1": "conform", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "trigger", "Opt_4": "appoint", "Answer": "trigger", "Opt_1_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school wanted to set up a new computer lab, but the ____ would have been too high.", "Opt_1": "expense", "Opt_2": "magnitude", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "community", "Answer": "expense", "Opt_1_def": "cost", "Opt_2_def": "size; amount", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is the completely rational response of a country that has no hope of defeating the United States in battle but ____ wants to insure that it isn't attacked.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "fairly", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Sufficient progress has been made with ____ to drinking water to place within reach the target of halving the proportion of the population without access to safe drinking water between 1990 and 2015.", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "undertake", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "regard", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is advisable that you put your name on these waiting lists ____ to your arrival.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Honesty is not an attribute that most people ____ with occupations such as politician or used-car salesman.", "Opt_1": "appear", "Opt_2": "dispose", "Opt_3": "resign", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_2_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Governments cannot govern without the ____ assent of the people.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "feasible", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "broad", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "possible", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Previous experience in such areas, especially microscopy, would be an ____ but is not essential.", "Opt_1": "strategy", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "advantage", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "benefit", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "No matter how good the lawyer's intuition and ability to express himself or herself, the lawyer will not ____ unless he or she can analyze logically.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "express", "Opt_3": "request", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "succeed", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "English may be a global language but it is not yet a proper ____ for exploring most of the world's societies and cultures.", "Opt_1": "tool", "Opt_2": "incident", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "scheme", "Answer": "tool", "Opt_1_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "happening; event", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "plan. idea, project"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is not necessarily subjected to a ____ analysis, thus it will need to be evaluated by the user.", "Opt_1": "thorough", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "equivalent", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is now ____ to almost everyone that the decision to invade Iraq was a very serious error of judgment.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "obvious", "Opt_3": "outstanding", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "obvious", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_3_def": "excellent", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Examples of everyday fitness programs include walking during lunch hour, parking farther away from one's place of work, and taking stairs ____ of an elevator.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There was a ____ demonstration on the streets of London to protest the government's plans to go to war in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "massive", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We should never praise or ____ any person on account of outward actions that are common to all; but only on account of their principles.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "repeat", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "blame", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to accuse"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Typically held the 3rd week of February, this is an annual ____ that helps College of Fine Arts students explore careers, develop strategies to pursue career and artistic goals successfully.", "Opt_1": "aim", "Opt_2": "assignment", "Opt_3": "property", "Opt_4": "event", "Answer": "event", "Opt_1_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_2_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_3_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_4_def": "a happening"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Strauss said his health started to ____ and he was placed on the transplant recipient waiting list.", "Opt_1": "contemplate", "Opt_2": "disturb", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "decline", "Opt_1_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The first and only ____ line of defense against the acquisition or use of \"suitcase nuclear weapons\"", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "reliable", "Opt_3": "extraordinary", "Opt_4": "significant", "Answer": "reliable", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "by terrorists lies in the countries that possess such devices.", "Opt_3_def": "very unusual", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In this paper we describe simple identification and signature schemes which ____ any user to prove his identity and the authenticity of his messages.", "Opt_1": "emerge", "Opt_2": "improve", "Opt_3": "persist", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_2_def": "to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The only ____ of having computers in the classroom is that they are loud and make the room hot.", "Opt_1": "deal", "Opt_2": "item", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "drawback", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "thing, element", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage, problem"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The work involves some lifting and bending, and ____ requires travel away from the normal duty station.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He told reporters that he did not want to intervene in the dispute over the ____ minister.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "prime", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "prime", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school is overspending and will soon ____ all the money set aside for books and other materials.", "Opt_1": "condemn", "Opt_2": "deteriorate", "Opt_3": "exhaust", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "exhaust", "Opt_1_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to use up", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The good results in recent matches ____ that the new trainer knows what he is doing.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "regard", "Opt_3": "damage", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "imply", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Digital Libraries constitute a relatively young scientific field, whose life spans ____ the last fifteen years.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "roughly", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "about, approximately"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In the 1850s, texts did not ____ widely enough to provoke a revolution.", "Opt_1": "isolate", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "extend", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Campuses must publish an annual security report detailing statistics ____ crimes committed on campus and at affiliated locations.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I do not ____ about your right to an opinion, but I do ____ about your inability to see the truth when it is explained to you.", "Opt_1": "presume", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "estimate", "Opt_4": "enter", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_4_def": "to go in or put in"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Hacking's book suffers from a serious defect, ____ he does not understand the nature of hypnosis.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "namely", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Research shows that earnings ____ strongly with IQ levels.", "Opt_1": "correlate", "Opt_2": "exist", "Opt_3": "conduct", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "correlate", "Opt_1_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_2_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_3_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The 7 Harry Potter books have been published at an ____ of about 2-3 years.", "Opt_1": "interval", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "authority", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "a period of time", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Parents often ____ their children's choice of clothes or music..", "Opt_1": "criticize", "Opt_2": "recognize", "Opt_3": "fare", "Opt_4": "establish", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_3_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_4_def": "to begin or set up"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He was highly confidential and did not ____ his (personal) accomplishments.", "Opt_1": "confirm", "Opt_2": "monitor", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "broadcast", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_2_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The death of Princess Diana was an ____ that shocked the whole world.", "Opt_1": "device", "Opt_2": "debate", "Opt_3": "interpretation", "Opt_4": "event", "Answer": "event", "Opt_1_def": "object; method", "Opt_2_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_3_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_4_def": "a happening"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "To develop a comprehensive approach to business, managers must ____ the strengths of their employees in assigning tasks.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "exist", "Opt_3": "utilize", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is evidence that increases in short sale transactions ____ stock price declines.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "decline", "Opt_3": "admit", "Opt_4": "provoke", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_4_def": "to cause to happen"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Politics is still a ____ male profession.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The new government plans to deliver the best possible health ____ for all of its citizens.", "Opt_1": "deed", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "an action", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There was little doubt that the government's plans to ____ taxes would be very unpopular.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "utilize", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "preserve", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon."}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is not difficult to ____ on what could happen to these laws if the computer really does change our attitude to knowledge.", "Opt_1": "transfer", "Opt_2": "speculate", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "disturb", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_2_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt, stop from working"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some scientists claim that we cannot ____ global warming on the basis of a just few years of hot weather.", "Opt_1": "purchase", "Opt_2": "convey", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "infer", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to buy", "Opt_2_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The pharmacy does not have access to your medical record, thus is unable to ____ insurance information from the health forms.", "Opt_1": "respect", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "accompany", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In the Fall of 1998, there was an ____ at a vehicle manufacturing plant involving a chemical shipment that was piped into the wrong tank.", "Opt_1": "background", "Opt_2": "principle", "Opt_3": "obligation", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "rule", "Opt_3_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I don't think the government will manage to ____ many people to recycle more of their garbage.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "require", "Opt_3": "acknowledge", "Opt_4": "persuade", "Answer": "persuade", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to need", "Opt_3_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_4_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Simply exporting ____ graduates is not itself a policy problem if there is a demand for those graduates.", "Opt_1": "surplus", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "surplus", "Opt_1_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "People might be surprised to know that a similar situation had occurred in the US and that doctors and hospitals were allowed to ____ the family's wishes.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "combine", "Opt_4": "qualify", "Answer": "override", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_4_def": "to become eligible"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She was very feminine, yet very strong, very ____ under the surface.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "tough", "Opt_4": "key", "Answer": "tough", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The twins ____ most of the weekend to their fishing hobby.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "deduce", "Opt_4": "revive", "Answer": "devote", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to bring back (to life)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Open Office Writer is ____ of saving documents in many different formats.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "independent", "Opt_3": "capable", "Opt_4": "trivial", "Answer": "capable", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_3_def": "able", "Opt_4_def": "not important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The drugs are used to ____ performance artificially to the degree that they give athletes a competitive edge.", "Opt_1": "reverse", "Opt_2": "enhance", "Opt_3": "exclude", "Opt_4": "denote", "Answer": "enhance", "Opt_1_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_2_def": "to make something better", "Opt_3_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A lasting peace in Iraq will remain but a ____ hope.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "passive", "Opt_3": "precise", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_3_def": "exact", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Powerpoint presentations do not always impress, ____ if the actual content is poor.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "especially", "Opt_4": "approximately", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "particularly", "Opt_4_def": "about; not exactly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school tried to ____ the fact that one of its teachers had a criminal record.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "confront", "Opt_4": "suppress", "Answer": "suppress", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We explain that at each movement in the dance there are endless opportunities to ____ new ideas.", "Opt_1": "evolve", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "strain", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "insert", "Opt_1_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "While we were not ____ surprised by the answers to our questions, it was interesting to see the amount of uniformity in answers.", "Opt_1": "moreover", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Medical scientists have done extensive research on individual drugs but they do not know so much how drugs ____ with each other.", "Opt_1": "preserve", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "confine", "Opt_4": "interact", "Answer": "interact", "Opt_1_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to react, to affect and be affected"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Trying to water-ski for the first time is difficult but if you keep practising, you will ____ learn how to do it.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "moreover", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Progress is so fast these days that some technological products become ____ within a very short time.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "obsolete", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "My parents will ____ that I did this work without help.", "Opt_1": "infer", "Opt_2": "verify", "Opt_3": "commence", "Opt_4": "permit", "Answer": "verify", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_2_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_3_def": "to start", "Opt_4_def": "to allow"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Iraqi regime failed to take that final opportunity to ____ with the United Nations investigation.", "Opt_1": "organize", "Opt_2": "terminate", "Opt_3": "cooperate", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "cooperate", "Opt_1_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_2_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "As migration is a spatial choice process, it is important to ____ how migrants perceive space and choose a destination in the space.", "Opt_1": "comprehend", "Opt_2": "enforce", "Opt_3": "distinguish", "Opt_4": "coordinate", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_3_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_4_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If he doesn't start to ____ his behaviour, he is in danger of being asked to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "contribute", "Opt_3": "trigger", "Opt_4": "undergo", "Answer": "amend", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_3_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_4_def": "to receive or experience"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The relationship between Christianity and the Enlightenment remains a ____ issue in the history of Western civilization.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "initial", "Opt_4": "major", "Answer": "vital", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "starting, first", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The new policy means that faculty members can no longer enter or ____ grades for these classes online.", "Opt_1": "demonstrate", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "exaggerate", "Opt_4": "modify", "Answer": "modify", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Musicians are listed alphabetically, but for some ____ reason Carter, Benny is listed after Carter, Ron.", "Opt_1": "latter", "Opt_2": "logical", "Opt_3": "odd", "Opt_4": "perpetual", "Answer": "odd", "Opt_1_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_2_def": "making sense", "Opt_3_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "His current measurement results are not ____ enough to identify exactly the minimum that the ball is sitting in.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "massive", "Opt_3": "precise", "Opt_4": "enormous", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "exact", "Opt_4_def": "very big"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Though all of them are presented in English, there is a significant contrast in clarity between the ____ reports.", "Opt_1": "various", "Opt_2": "adjacent", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "immense", "Answer": "various", "Opt_1_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_2_def": "next to", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We southerners, and especially we white southerners, owe a huge ____ to valiant civil rights leaders like Martin Luther King.", "Opt_1": "stage", "Opt_2": "sphere", "Opt_3": "truth", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "debt", "Opt_1_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest", "Opt_3_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Calderone's insistence that sex education should begin as early as kindergarten did not ____ religious conservative groups.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "suggest", "Opt_3": "unite", "Opt_4": "impress", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to create a favourable reaction"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you ____ against the school's computer use policy, you will not be permitted to use the computer labs.", "Opt_1": "represent", "Opt_2": "expel", "Opt_3": "offend", "Opt_4": "descend", "Answer": "offend", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_2_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_3_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_4_def": "to go down"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Aside from the significant ____ impact of the bill, it carries little weight and makes little difference.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "remote", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "political", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "School need to ____ their curricula on the needs of the students who attend them.", "Opt_1": "suspend", "Opt_2": "eliminate", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_2_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The student's answer may not ____ all parts of the question or may demonstrate an inaccurate or superficial analysis of the passage.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "realize", "Opt_3": "convey", "Opt_4": "address", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_3_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_4_def": "to give attention to (an issue)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "At no point in our deliberations are numbers employed in a way that would trigger an ____ decision to offer or deny admission.", "Opt_1": "legal", "Opt_2": "ultimate", "Opt_3": "spontaneous", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_2_def": "final or most important", "Opt_3_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A color model is an orderly system for creating a whole ____ of colors from a small set of primary colors.", "Opt_1": "ignorance", "Opt_2": "conflict", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "range", "Opt_1_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_2_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The fact that speech is ____ to result in some violence or in destruction of property is not enough to justify its suppression.", "Opt_1": "logical", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "making sense", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some people use unethical methods to ____ a statistic that says what they want it to say.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "fluctuate", "Opt_4": "create", "Answer": "create", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_4_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I need to speak to John's parents ____ his constant absence.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Compliment employees in public but always ____ them in private; this shows your respect for them and avoids embarrassment.", "Opt_1": "reject", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "assemble", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Teachers must ____ students and supervise activities in the computer room.", "Opt_1": "deserve", "Opt_2": "accompany", "Opt_3": "destroy", "Opt_4": "cooperate", "Answer": "accompany", "Opt_1_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_2_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_3_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_4_def": "to work (well) with another person"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has banned smoking in ____ all public places.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "virtually", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The number of students in the school will continue to ____ in the next few years as Frankfurt increases in popularity.", "Opt_1": "diverge", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "correspond", "Opt_4": "multiply", "Answer": "multiply", "Opt_1_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to be related to", "Opt_4_def": "to increase greatly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Compliment employees in public but always ____ them in private; this shows your respect for them and avoids embarrassment.", "Opt_1": "isolate", "Opt_2": "reject", "Opt_3": "focus", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse", "Opt_3_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This forecast showed much less ____ than expected by the district's officials and residents.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "source", "Opt_4": "device", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_4_def": "object; method"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Since the U.S. flu vaccine supply was cut in half early this month, shots are scarce, lines long and some people are ____ to miss out.", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "permanent", "Opt_3": "certain", "Opt_4": "military", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_3_def": "sure", "Opt_4_def": "to do with army"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The report was designed to measure computer and Internet use ____ people with disabilities.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Before economists ____ drastic measures to reduce population growth, further studies should be performed.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "refute", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Every ____ effort will be made to accommodate properly documented special needs.", "Opt_1": "constant", "Opt_2": "fortunate", "Opt_3": "permanent", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_2_def": "lucky", "Opt_3_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "An ____ of English that many learners find difficult is verb grammar.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "aspect", "Opt_3": "instinct", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "aspect", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_3_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In history lessons we learn about many ____ peoples such as the Egyptians who built the pyramids, and Roman emperors like Julius Caesar.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "loose", "Opt_3": "ancient", "Opt_4": "enormous", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_3_def": "very old", "Opt_4_def": "very big"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It was in 1827, near the beginning of his time ____ from the Allan family, that Poe witnessed his first collection of poetry.", "Opt_1": "evident", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "apart", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "clear", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "not together, separate"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Of the questions asked in this section of the survey, having an ____ privacy policy is one of the highest percentage of responses.", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "thorough", "Opt_3": "explicit", "Opt_4": "abundant", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_3_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_4_def": "existing in large quantities"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There are strict laws that govern the ____ in rainforest wood.", "Opt_1": "settle", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "trade", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange products or services"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Survey show that women in American don't ____ their most serious health risk.", "Opt_1": "recognize", "Opt_2": "broadcast", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "establish", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_2_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to begin or set up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school offers Latin but there is no ____ for the subject among teachers and parents.", "Opt_1": "license", "Opt_2": "guarantee", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_2_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It's always better to be ____ cautious and to protect yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "thus", "Opt_2": "fairly", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "so", "Opt_2_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "too"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A simple and often ____ means to reduce blood pressure is to reduce the volume of body fluid with a diuretic.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "effective", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "abstract", "Answer": "effective", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "good, working well", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "not specific or concrete"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She says she's not a very good pianist, but I know that the ____ is true and she's just being modest.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "property", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "contrary", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The advice does not ____ to adults, only to children.", "Opt_1": "condemn", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "deteriorate", "Opt_4": "apply", "Answer": "apply", "Opt_1_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to be relevant (to)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Problems in school often ____ problems at home.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "extend", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "accompany", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government's ____ is that the bomb was set off by a recent immigrant.", "Opt_1": "substitute", "Opt_2": "theory", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "status", "Answer": "theory", "Opt_1_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_2_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "position, standing"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is a ____ that Japanese girls are quiet. You should hear them on the bus on a school trip!", "Opt_1": "issue", "Opt_2": "substitute", "Opt_3": "administration", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_2_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_3_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Soviet nationality studies ____ that the state was not able to eliminate discrimination based on ethnicity.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "demonstrate", "Opt_3": "intervene", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "demonstrate", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is not in employers' interest to get rid of cheap illegal immigrants - only to ____ them of any rights.", "Opt_1": "encounter", "Opt_2": "preserve", "Opt_3": "train", "Opt_4": "deprive", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_2_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_3_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "to take away (the opportunity)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You need to ____ your work a little more closely for silly spelling or punctuation errors.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "spread", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government minister expressed regret at her thoughtless ____ about 'lazy incompetent teachers'.", "Opt_1": "means", "Opt_2": "comment", "Opt_3": "battle", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "comment", "Opt_1_def": "way", "Opt_2_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_3_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She has continued ____ me with her hard work and positive attitude.", "Opt_1": "impress", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "culminate", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to end", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It should be obvious that the consumption habits of the wealthy countries are the ____ cause of environmental problems.", "Opt_1": "tough", "Opt_2": "prime", "Opt_3": "proper", "Opt_4": "vague", "Answer": "prime", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Children who have no ____ to their behaviour are often unhappy.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "boundary", "Opt_3": "expense", "Opt_4": "member", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_3_def": "cost", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is our belief that the students were not given a fair hearing, and ____ that the punishment was unjust.", "Opt_1": "perhaps", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "conversely", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "furthermore", "Opt_1_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has increased the tax on petrol, ____ making itself very unpopular with motorists.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian region have in common ____ being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The course is ____ concerned with the social relations of power that developed along with the major revolutionary currents of the eighteenth century.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "fairly", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "quite, somewhat"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The airport police always ____ the need for everyone to be vigilant with their suitcases and other bags.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "provide", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "stress", "Answer": "stress", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to give", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some government decisions are made for political reasons and others for ____ reasons.", "Opt_1": "precise", "Opt_2": "average", "Opt_3": "equivalent", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "exact", "Opt_2_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_3_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You can submit your work at any time ____ to the due date.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He was absent yesterday for the third time this month. I ____ he has been having problems with his back again.", "Opt_1": "retain", "Opt_2": "stipulate", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "presume", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to require", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to believe, assume"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He ____ failed to mention the unfortunate fact that he had dropped out of college.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Eat less, exercise more: the ____ for weight loss is so simple, yet so hard.", "Opt_1": "formula", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "duty", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is ____ unusual considering the 1997 survey's response of 41%.", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some institutions did not ____ these issues because they predicted them and dealt with them in advance.", "Opt_1": "deprive", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "resign", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government does not plan to ____ any more immigrants unless they can prove that their life is in danger in their own country.", "Opt_1": "append", "Opt_2": "deteriorate", "Opt_3": "admit", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "admit", "Opt_1_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The study finds they are more likely than their non-Latino white neighbors to ____ another stroke in the first two years after living through one.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "join", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "reserve", "Answer": "suffer", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The war in Iraq serves to ____ the government's unwillingness to listen to the wishes of the majority of its people.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "react", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to respond"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She did not follow the ____ on the label, despite carefully reading it.", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "prestige", "Opt_4": "decade", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_4_def": "a period of ten years"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A verbal ____ is impossible to prove, and the organization will always maintain that it was a misunderstanding.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "contract", "Opt_3": "component", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_3_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She had shown no ____ to engage in abusive conduct.", "Opt_1": "propensity", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "grant", "Opt_4": "attitude", "Answer": "propensity", "Opt_1_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_4_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You need to ____ a little more time to your studies and a little less time to your sports.", "Opt_1": "dedicate", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "approach", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to near; to get closer"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is difficult for the government to ____ money fairly to all the organizations that need financial help.", "Opt_1": "arise", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "approve", "Opt_4": "earn", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to agree to", "Opt_4_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If UVA is to increase ____ of satisfaction among junior faculty, it must make an effort to align its policies and practices more closely with the needs and expectations of the faculty.", "Opt_1": "intention", "Opt_2": "motive", "Opt_3": "level", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "level", "Opt_1_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_2_def": "reason", "Opt_3_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Furthermore, as an educational institution, the College cannot ignore the background and perspectives of its students and must ____ to promote teaching practices and a campus atmosphere that benefits and ensures the success of all of its learners.", "Opt_1": "offer", "Opt_2": "oppose", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "attempt", "Answer": "attempt", "Opt_1_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_2_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to try"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ for oil is likely to increase as people in developing countries such as China and India acquire cars.", "Opt_1": "friction", "Opt_2": "affair", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Nature was an ____ part of ancient Chinese, Japanese, and Indian literature.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "key", "Opt_3": "flexible", "Opt_4": "outstanding", "Answer": "intrinsic", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_4_def": "excellent"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some students claim that they can ____ watch TV and do their homework.", "Opt_1": "nevertheless", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "accordingly", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We designed an ____ to acquire blood from embryonic rats.", "Opt_1": "alternative", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "other possibility", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is difficult to ____ the importance of the internet.", "Opt_1": "depart", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A significant ____ of winning the bid for the next Olympic Games is that it will cost the country an enormous amount of money.", "Opt_1": "symbol", "Opt_2": "drawback", "Opt_3": "statement", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_3_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Each College or School should ____ the teaching of basic technology skills at the earliest level possible.", "Opt_1": "conceal", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "integrate", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to hide", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to fit into a new situation"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many people believe that the 'war on terror' will be a ____ war.", "Opt_1": "essential", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "fortunate", "Opt_4": "perpetual", "Answer": "perpetual", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "lucky", "Opt_4_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He uses Blanche White to ____ the problems of color and class difference between blacks and whites.", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "conserve", "Opt_3": "expose", "Opt_4": "proceed", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_3_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_4_def": "to go forward (and do ..)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Thus, there is no question but that the donor intends this gift to be for the ____ use of Princeton University.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "sole", "Opt_3": "distinct", "Opt_4": "radical", "Answer": "sole", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "only", "Opt_3_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_4_def": "extreme, strong"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It was given to the grandmother by her grandfather in 1852, when the ____ was a member of the California assembly.", "Opt_1": "intense", "Opt_2": "rational", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "straightforward", "Answer": "latter", "Opt_1_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_2_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is not clear to me how you can ____ make cannabis legal and expect the consumption of it to go down.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The aim of the proposal is to ____ people of the liberty to download songs and videos from the internet.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "trigger", "Opt_3": "deprive", "Opt_4": "risk", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_3_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The revolutionary impulse must come from those ____ human needs that are failed by capitalism.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most people today agree with the ____ that men and women are equal.", "Opt_1": "surface", "Opt_2": "growth", "Opt_3": "schedule", "Opt_4": "notion", "Answer": "notion", "Opt_1_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_2_def": "development, increase", "Opt_3_def": "timetable", "Opt_4_def": "idea; concept"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "English may be a ____ language but it is not yet a proper tool for exploring most of the world's societies and cultures.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "royal", "Opt_3": "global", "Opt_4": "wise", "Answer": "global", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_3_def": "world", "Opt_4_def": "intelligent; sensible"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Your target heart ____ is a useful way of pacing yourself during exercise.", "Opt_1": "ignorance", "Opt_2": "scale", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_2_def": "extent", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In August, UMBC will ____ a new home page on our Web site.", "Opt_1": "possess", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "launch", "Opt_4": "admit", "Answer": "launch", "Opt_1_def": "to have or own", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to begin", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to enter"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Various approaches to environmental justice are discussed, along with steps in the planning process when ____ involvement is particularly effective.", "Opt_1": "magnitude", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "citizen", "Opt_4": "error", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "size; amount", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_4_def": "a mistake"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "People might be surprised to know that a similar situation had occurred in the US and that doctors and hospitals were allowed to ____ the family's wishes.", "Opt_1": "override", "Opt_2": "contribute", "Opt_3": "represent", "Opt_4": "offer", "Answer": "override", "Opt_1_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_2_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_4_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The district cannot ____ the accuracy of the information or the appropriateness of any material that a student finds.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "section", "Opt_3": "display", "Opt_4": "guarantee", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "part", "Opt_3_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_4_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Individuals should report the incident to a faculty or staff ____ at the university with whom they are comfortable.", "Opt_1": "member", "Opt_2": "sequence", "Opt_3": "boundary", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_2_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_3_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Are you conscious of the fact that you may ____ the course?", "Opt_1": "exceed", "Opt_2": "provide", "Opt_3": "fail", "Opt_4": "react", "Answer": "fail", "Opt_1_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_2_def": "to give", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_4_def": "to respond"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some people ____ that the reasons for invading Iraq were to gain control of its oil.", "Opt_1": "resign", "Opt_2": "contain", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Candidates must ____ a high level of responsibility, the ability to work independently, and a strong commitment to customer service.", "Opt_1": "enlarge", "Opt_2": "demonstrate", "Opt_3": "refer", "Opt_4": "assure", "Answer": "demonstrate", "Opt_1_def": "to make larger", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Be certain to answer the question in its entirety. Be certain to explain how and why you came to a ____ conclusion.", "Opt_1": "typical", "Opt_2": "familiar", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "particular", "Opt_1_def": "usual", "Opt_2_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "All of his projects ____ the idea of flexibility within different, changing environments.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school's facilities have been improved ____ with the addition of a second library and media centre.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "recently", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "in the near past", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Yoo Jong-pil, spokesman of the DP, claimed Roh wanted to further distinguish himself from the ____ government and humiliate the DP.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "previous", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "previous", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "the one before", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It was a very elementary problem. All the students were able to ____ it within 5 minutes.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "solve", "Opt_3": "determine", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "solve", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This was not ____ of Serbia alone; the population felt similar frustration in other parts of Yugoslavia and in Eastern Europe.", "Opt_1": "characteristic", "Opt_2": "uniform", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "elaborate", "Answer": "characteristic", "Opt_1_def": "typical", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "detailed; complex"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He was ____ yesterday for the third time this month. I presume he has been having problems with his back again.", "Opt_1": "homogeneous", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "diverse", "Opt_4": "precise", "Answer": "absent", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "many and different", "Opt_4_def": "exact"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He told reporters that he did not want to ____ in the dispute over the prime minister.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "improve", "Opt_3": "refer", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "intervene", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The mask must always ____ the actor in expressing both joy and grief.", "Opt_1": "inhibit", "Opt_2": "comprise", "Opt_3": "react", "Opt_4": "contemplate", "Answer": "inhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_3_def": "to respond", "Opt_4_def": "to think about; to consider"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "While addiction and drugs are serious problems in society that ____ a humane approach, there is no room for nonsense if we want to achieve success.", "Opt_1": "align", "Opt_2": "require", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "require", "Opt_1_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_2_def": "to need", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "What's the ____ time needed to finish a course?", "Opt_1": "average", "Opt_2": "royal", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "characteristic", "Answer": "average", "Opt_1_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_2_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "typical"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The donors specified that they would like to help hardworking students with medium grades who ____ help.", "Opt_1": "stimulate", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "provide", "Opt_4": "compel", "Answer": "deserve", "Opt_1_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to give", "Opt_4_def": "to force or make happen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school offers Latin but there is no ____ for the subject among teachers and parents.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "access", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "exhibit", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She is yet to master ____ verb grammar. She often says He do .. instead of He does ...", "Opt_1": "visual", "Opt_2": "basic", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_2_def": "first or easy", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "They found that specific, simple steps can ____ reduce the number of drivers who drink.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "hence", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "rather", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "instead"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The main ____ of a good teacher is knowledge of his or her subject.", "Opt_1": "privilege", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "attribute", "Answer": "attribute", "Opt_1_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; property"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The headmaster called a meeting to try to ____ the dispute between the two teachers.", "Opt_1": "convey", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "cease", "Opt_4": "settle", "Answer": "settle", "Opt_1_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to solve a problem or dispute"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The company does a minor ____ of business in the USA; the majority of its trade is in Europe.", "Opt_1": "rank", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "amount", "Opt_4": "alternative", "Answer": "amount", "Opt_1_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "other possibility"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school is trying to ____ reading by having a small library of books in every classroom.", "Opt_1": "insist", "Opt_2": "appeal", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "promote", "Answer": "promote", "Opt_1_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_2_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If there is an item that you need quickly, please ____ the time frame within which you need it.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "justice", "Opt_3": "penalty", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_3_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The New Investigator Competition is an award for the best paper by a graduate student, carrying with it a prize valued at ____ \ufffd\ufffd500.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In a densely populated area, an earthquake may do far more damage than one of greater ____ that occurs in a remote area.", "Opt_1": "field", "Opt_2": "circumstances", "Opt_3": "sphere", "Opt_4": "magnitude", "Answer": "magnitude", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_2_def": "situation", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest", "Opt_4_def": "size; amount"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ability to communicate accurately and effectively is a ____ component of the curriculum.", "Opt_1": "arbitrary", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "spontaneous", "Opt_4": "strict", "Answer": "vital", "Opt_1_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_4_def": "hard, not changeable"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Mathews touches on an ____ that has puzzled students of American regional religious history.", "Opt_1": "domain", "Opt_2": "anomaly", "Opt_3": "mechanism", "Opt_4": "evidence", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_3_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_4_def": "proof, signs"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We got some very ____ results in our science experiment. I think the thermometer was not working correctly.", "Opt_1": "cautious", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "careful", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Nadeem has worked with FSU London since early 2004 as a permanent ____ of staff managing the Information Technology Systems.", "Opt_1": "member", "Opt_2": "implication", "Opt_3": "environment", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_2_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_3_def": "the world around us", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You will need to provide a sample of recent writing so that your English ____ can be assessed.", "Opt_1": "feature", "Opt_2": "notion", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "level", "Opt_1_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_2_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is no point having a law if the police are not willing to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "enforce", "Opt_4": "amend", "Answer": "enforce", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_4_def": "to change (usually to improve something)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government failed to understand why the people were so unhappy with its policies, and ____ was voted out at the next election.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "roughly", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "about, approximately"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "By performing better than humanly possible, the robots will ____ humans from essential roles.", "Opt_1": "require", "Opt_2": "displace", "Opt_3": "consist", "Opt_4": "suppress", "Answer": "displace", "Opt_1_def": "to need", "Opt_2_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Attendance will not constitute a specific percentage of your final grade, but if you miss more than two classes you will ____ fail this course.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He did not get a positive response to his ____ for a day's absence from work.", "Opt_1": "deserve", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "request", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "request", "Opt_1_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Given the abundance of oxygen and silicon in the crust, it should not be surprising that the most ____ minerals in the earth's crust are the silicates.", "Opt_1": "rare", "Opt_2": "abundant", "Opt_3": "profound", "Opt_4": "willing", "Answer": "abundant", "Opt_1_def": "unusual", "Opt_2_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_3_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_4_def": "happy or prepared to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This widespread ____ was caused by the insufficient amount of media coverage on topic.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "duty", "Opt_4": "guide", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_4_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The unpleasant ____ in the computer lab is sure to occupy my thoughts in the next few days.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "bias", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "function", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "job or role"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government is taking advice from experts on how to ____ the increase of illegal immigrants.", "Opt_1": "degenerate", "Opt_2": "halt", "Opt_3": "master", "Opt_4": "seek", "Answer": "halt", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_4_def": "to look for or want"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A student enrolled in these types of courses really didn't get to know the instructor well and ____ did not feel any sense of community.", "Opt_1": "perhaps", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The war in Iraq serves to ____ the government's unwillingness to listen to the wishes of the majority of its people.", "Opt_1": "illustrate", "Opt_2": "dismiss", "Opt_3": "survive", "Opt_4": "suffer", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_2_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_3_def": "to not die", "Opt_4_def": "to experience something bad or painful"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The media and the public should not ____ the music industry for the jobs that parents are not fulfilling.", "Opt_1": "owe", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "elect", "Opt_4": "blame", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_4_def": "to accuse"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ between Russia's dominant military power and our own inferior power could not be bridged overnight.", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "performance", "Opt_3": "gap", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "gap", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_3_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We engage outside ____ to work on particular matters when considerations such as cost and highly specialized subject matter make it appropriate to do so.", "Opt_1": "agent", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "tradition", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Archaeologists found some Roman coins ____ the town wall.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If we accept your request to ____ the information, we will make reasonable efforts to inform others, including people you have authorized, of the ____ment.", "Opt_1": "emphasize", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "amend", "Opt_4": "fare", "Answer": "amend", "Opt_1_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_4_def": "to do or succeed"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We need to put our minds together and decide if we need to collaborate among our institutions to ____ a new service.", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "undergo", "Opt_3": "amend", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "provide", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you decide to apply, you will need to ____ a full application including: cover sheet, goals and plan letter, and project statement.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "fluctuate", "Opt_3": "indicate", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_3_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Typically held the 3rd week of February, this is an annual event that helps College of Fine Arts students ____ careers, develop strategies to pursue career and artistic goals successfully.", "Opt_1": "explore", "Opt_2": "reduce", "Opt_3": "deviate", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_2_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_3_def": "to be different", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I usually keep a supply of ____ pencils in my desk, so that I can lend one to any student who comes without.", "Opt_1": "vast", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "average", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "spare", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school plans to ____ the sports field so that games can be played after dark.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "motivate", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "illuminate", "Answer": "illuminate", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to show clearly; to light up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You have learned this lesson that water and other liquids transmit ____ better than air.", "Opt_1": "satisfactory", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "sound", "Opt_4": "effective", "Answer": "sound", "Opt_1_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "good; strong", "Opt_4_def": "good, working well"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The partners realized that their small fund was not sufficient to support early stage start-ups in the ____ of the early 2000s.", "Opt_1": "asset", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "bias", "Opt_4": "supply", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_4_def": "provision, store"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is hardly a surprise that national governments have failed to solve global problems, since they have also failed to solve their own ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "homogeneous", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "domestic", "Opt_4": "obvious", "Answer": "domestic", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "home", "Opt_4_def": "clear, evident"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Upon completion of the course, students will be able to discern how grammar and usage errors can ____ with meaning.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "employ", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "accompany", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most educational institutions have a required ____ for citations and references.", "Opt_1": "statement", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "format", "Opt_1_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Simply exporting surplus graduates is not itself a policy problem if there is a ____ for those graduates.", "Opt_1": "object", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "portion", "Opt_4": "affair", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "thing", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "part, amount", "Opt_4_def": "an event or series of events"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "These programs must ____ factors that may be affecting profits.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "evaluate", "Opt_3": "enhance", "Opt_4": "present", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "to make something better", "Opt_4_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "From the quality of the writing I can only ____ that someone helped him. His work is usually nowhere near as good.", "Opt_1": "encounter", "Opt_2": "infer", "Opt_3": "confront", "Opt_4": "discern", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_3_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to perceive"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Including future irrelevant costs ____ will not lead to a poor choice; it will only complicate the analysis.", "Opt_1": "definitely", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Teachers ____ that students will be negatively affected by the construction of a new road just outside many of the classrooms.", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "exclude", "Opt_3": "strive", "Opt_4": "suspend", "Answer": "fear", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_3_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_4_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Little ____ has been made in negotiations to free the Koreans kidnapped in Afghanistan,.", "Opt_1": "outline", "Opt_2": "forecast", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "progress", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_2_def": "prediction", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "improvement or development"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Next you need to ____ a search statement so you can conduct a database search.", "Opt_1": "appeal", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "formulate", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "formulate", "Opt_1_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to express", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The contributors ____ that teaching is a gendered occupation with low status and relatively low pay.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "assert", "Opt_3": "classify", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Can you please give me the final ____ of your writing? This looks like your first draft before you corrected the spelling and grammar.", "Opt_1": "decade", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "reluctance", "Answer": "version", "Opt_1_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "unwillingness; hesitation"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some scientists claim that we cannot ____ global warming on the basis of a just few years of hot weather.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "speculate", "Opt_3": "infer", "Opt_4": "conserve", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_4_def": "to preserve; to not use"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "As a result of the ____ amount of evidence for evolution accumulated over the last two centuries, we can safely conclude that evolution has occurred.", "Opt_1": "relevant", "Opt_2": "elementary", "Opt_3": "massive", "Opt_4": "arbitrary", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The whole new industry of purchasing drugs \"on line\" is another area where care and ____ sense are essential.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "public", "Opt_4": "instant", "Answer": "common", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_4_def": "immediate"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Be certain to answer the question in its entirety. Be certain to ____ how and why you came to a particular conclusion.", "Opt_1": "explain", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "advance", "Answer": "explain", "Opt_1_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to go or move forward; to get better"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "His lungs were filled in an ____ with a great volume of driven air which he could not expel.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "ultimate", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "instant", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "final or most important", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "immediate"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Nine tenths of an iceberg is under water and ____ invisible to ships.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "respectively", "Answer": "hence", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I ____ that problems at home are the reason for her poor performance in school.", "Opt_1": "withdraw", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "suspect", "Opt_1_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Burning of coal is a ____ way to obtain energy, but it creates a serious amount of pollution.", "Opt_1": "convenient", "Opt_2": "preliminary", "Opt_3": "explicit", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_2_def": "first; initial", "Opt_3_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She is so passive in German class. It's no wonder that she can ____ speak a word of the language.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "hardly", "Opt_4": "accordingly", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "not very much", "Opt_4_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It's not easy to ____ yourself when you're not going out and actually preparing for an opponent.", "Opt_1": "motivate", "Opt_2": "sustain", "Opt_3": "observe", "Opt_4": "assume", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_3_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Such activity cannot be considered an ____ substitute for excellence in teaching and research.", "Opt_1": "numerous", "Opt_2": "elaborate", "Opt_3": "deficient", "Opt_4": "adequate", "Answer": "adequate", "Opt_1_def": "very many", "Opt_2_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_3_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_4_def": "good enough; ok"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Humans have a strong ____ to help each other, but is spite also part of the human condition?", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "target", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "constraint", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to prevent"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The purpose of this study was to explore the internal and external factors influencing the career development of first ____ Filipina Americans.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "constraint", "Opt_3": "period", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "generation", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_3_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is still too soon to say whether the invasion of Iraq was ____ it.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school is will ____ to undergo problems in its attempt to attract new students unless it reduces its tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "announce", "Opt_2": "attain", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "continue", "Answer": "continue", "Opt_1_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_2_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to carry on, not stop"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is scheduled to begin at 3:30 p.m. A decision to cancel or ____ the match will be made later in the day, if necessary.", "Opt_1": "motivate", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "combine", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Students are able to use basic communication and mathematics skills for purposes and situations they will ____ throughout their lives.", "Opt_1": "encounter", "Opt_2": "oppose", "Opt_3": "retain", "Opt_4": "adhere", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to keep to; to follow"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Every 10 years the government carries out a ____ survey of all households in the country. This is called a census.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "authentic", "Opt_3": "abstract", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_3_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The administrative staff will ____ the student supervisor when a student has failed to provide required documents and other ____ation.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "convince", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Colorado State University scientists have found a way to ____ improve the quality of laser light at extremely short wavelengths.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "What is your ____ of his recent odd behaviour?", "Opt_1": "interpretation", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "income", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "interpretation", "Opt_1_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "money earned", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Most leadership training programs leave out the key question, ____ how leaders actually affect their groups.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "recently", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "in the near past", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Advertising often tries to promote the idea that the customer deserves to buy the product because they are ____ it!", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "During the ____ of time that a student is on probation, any further instance of misconduct will cause the Board seriously to consider requiring the student to withdraw from the College.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "period", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "control"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It's no surprise that she is so quiet in class. She can ____ speak a word of English.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Our ____ was to determine whether the association between HPV infection and cervical cancer is consistent worldwide.", "Opt_1": "aim", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "aim", "Opt_1_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Simply exporting ____ graduates is not itself a policy problem if there is a demand for those graduates.", "Opt_1": "interior", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "surplus", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "surplus", "Opt_1_def": "inside", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you offend ____ the school's computer use policy, you will not be permitted to use the computer labs.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Colorado State University scientists have found a way to ____ improve the quality of laser light at extremely short wavelengths.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "especially", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "particularly", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We should avoid the error of assuming that we will ever be able to ____ the causes of his behaviour.", "Opt_1": "judge", "Opt_2": "provoke", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We still don't know if this is really the correct ____ to explain the imbalance between matter and antimatter that we observe.", "Opt_1": "task", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "limit", "Opt_4": "community", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "job", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Attendance will not ____ a specific percentage of your final grade, but if you miss more than two classes you will definitely fail this course.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "constitute", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The company's efforts to increase business over the past year failed to ____ the shareholders.", "Opt_1": "impress", "Opt_2": "discern", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Her family were persecuted by the Nazis, so it's no surprise that she shows ____ against the Germans.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "bias", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "sequence", "Answer": "bias", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "To ____ this from happening, it is very helpful for patients to avoid talking unless absolutely necessary for three days following surgery.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "damage", "Opt_3": "prefer", "Opt_4": "commit", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to like better", "Opt_4_def": "to do (often an offense)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Less educated minority parents are more likely to manifest a ____ of involvement in their child's schooling.", "Opt_1": "location", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "fee", "Opt_4": "evidence", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_4_def": "proof, signs"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school offers Latin but there is no demand for the subject ____ teachers and parents.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Since exactly the same language can be used by those who disagree with him, the ____ is too general to be of any use.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "course", "Answer": "theory", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "a subject or period of study"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "What we are really discussing is whether the industrialized countries can ____ the pensions promised by their respective governments.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "pursue", "Opt_3": "compel", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_3_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "At no ____ in our deliberations are numbers employed in a way that would trigger an automatic decision to offer or deny admission.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "journey", "Opt_4": "bulk", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_4_def": "majority; largest part"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "While you may not admit to political pressure, you must be aware of its almost constant presence; and you must ____ it and be prepared to deal with it.", "Opt_1": "convince", "Opt_2": "retire", "Opt_3": "recognize", "Opt_4": "ban", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_2_def": "to stop working", "Opt_3_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_4_def": "to prohibit or forbid"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If we learn to communicate effectively with others and are willing to ____ sharing our own feelings and respect other's feelings, many rewards will await us.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "risk", "Opt_3": "annotate", "Opt_4": "remain", "Answer": "risk", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_3_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to stay; still exist"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Today women and men have the same ____ in western society. This wasn't always the case.", "Opt_1": "ignorance", "Opt_2": "margin", "Opt_3": "level", "Opt_4": "status", "Answer": "status", "Opt_1_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_2_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_3_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_4_def": "position, standing"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is ____ unusual considering the 1997 survey's response of 41%.", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "so"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "US companies have too often viewed the social sector as a dumping ground for their spare cash, ____ equipment, and tired executives.", "Opt_1": "sufficient", "Opt_2": "logical", "Opt_3": "prime", "Opt_4": "obsolete", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "enough", "Opt_2_def": "making sense", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When does the unborn baby become an entity ____ from its mother?", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "evaluate", "Opt_3": "comply", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "separate", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A verbal ____ is impossible to prove, and the organization will always maintain that it was a misunderstanding.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "task", "Opt_4": "term", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "job", "Opt_4_def": "a word or expression"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "While a considerable degree of agreement was attained, a uniform approach to food ____ could not be reached.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "substitute", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Unilateralism may not be destroying American foreign ____ as some allege. But it does have its price.", "Opt_1": "labour", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "work", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government took the ____ decision to decrease tax.", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "profound", "Opt_3": "bold", "Opt_4": "prime", "Answer": "bold", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_3_def": "brave", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You will gain no credit for work that has ____ been copied from the internet.", "Opt_1": "absolutely", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I ____ the reasons for your failure to hand in the work on time. Nevertheless, our policy requires me to give you a zero.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "reform", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "appreciate", "Answer": "appreciate", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government expects to ____ resistance from some people to the prohibition of smoking in public places.", "Opt_1": "reduce", "Opt_2": "overcome", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "commence", "Answer": "overcome", "Opt_1_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_2_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to start"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Neither of the two strategies was ____ in terms of performance.", "Opt_1": "perpetual", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "efficient", "Opt_1_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The organizations that take credit for putting ecology first have failed to ____ or develop a system that will allow them to achieve their goals.", "Opt_1": "reform", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "stimulate", "Opt_4": "view", "Answer": "reform", "Opt_1_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_4_def": "to have an opinion"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She has made ____ good progress this year, but I still think she could have done better if she had tried harder.", "Opt_1": "furthermore", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is often impossible to ____ the pronunciation of a word from its spelling alone.", "Opt_1": "accept", "Opt_2": "require", "Opt_3": "infer", "Opt_4": "react", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_2_def": "to need", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_4_def": "to respond"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You have learned this lesson that water and other liquids transmit ____ better than air.", "Opt_1": "compulsory", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "deficient", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "sound", "Opt_1_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The temperatures did not ____ as much this month as they did last month.", "Opt_1": "protect", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "fluctuate", "Opt_4": "correlate", "Answer": "fluctuate", "Opt_1_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_4_def": "to have a close connection"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If we want to ____ support for an open and dynamic economy, our programs need to become as flexible and adaptable as the economy itself.", "Opt_1": "magnify", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "destroy", "Answer": "maintain", "Opt_1_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to break or damage completely"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you ____ your efforts you have a good chance of exiting ESL at the end of the year.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "sustain", "Opt_3": "conserve", "Opt_4": "arise", "Answer": "sustain", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_3_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_4_def": "to happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The accident was clearly not the ____ of the employee or his supervisor.", "Opt_1": "fault", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "fragment", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "fault", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "part of something", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school is planning to ____ its lunchtime sports program after hearing a request from the student council.", "Opt_1": "broadcast", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "revive", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "revive", "Opt_1_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The prompt response of the Hu Jintao government has won ____ praise, both inside and outside China.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "final", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "vague", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "last", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Be sure to ask if this is a good time to ____ the professor for your specific need.", "Opt_1": "destroy", "Opt_2": "recur", "Opt_3": "remove", "Opt_4": "approach", "Answer": "approach", "Opt_1_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_2_def": "to happen again", "Opt_3_def": "to take away", "Opt_4_def": "to near; to get closer"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Car companies spend a considerable ____ of money advertising their products.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "choice", "Opt_4": "sum", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_4_def": "an amount of money, total"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Military historians and other students of international security, gradually got into the ____ of meeting together to discuss ideas.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "diagnosis", "Opt_4": "domain", "Answer": "habit", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is the job of the brain to ____ all the body systems.", "Opt_1": "raise", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "coordinate", "Answer": "coordinate", "Opt_1_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He was absent yesterday for the third time this month. I ____ he has been having problems with his back again.", "Opt_1": "presume", "Opt_2": "owe", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "behave", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_2_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to act or do things in a certain way"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many people ____ before eating raw fish for the first time. They are not sure what it will taste like.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "hesitate", "Opt_3": "convince", "Opt_4": "dedicate", "Answer": "hesitate", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_4_def": "to devote (time and attention)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "His beliefs were not ____ enough to withstand the influence of the people worked with.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "firm", "Opt_3": "faint", "Opt_4": "vague", "Answer": "firm", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_3_def": "not strong", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The names of new products such as cars are not chosen at random. A large amount of research goes into choosing the most ____ name.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "permanent", "Opt_4": "suitable", "Answer": "suitable", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_4_def": "good for a particular job or purpose"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The workers participated in an ____ to see if they worked harder with music in the background.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "function", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "job or role"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We would probably become engaged in discussions from which we could not extract ourselves and ____ our freedom of action would be limited.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "perhaps", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government failed to keep its promises and ____ was voted out of power at the next election.", "Opt_1": "hence", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Humans have a strong ____ to help each other, but is spite also part of the human condition?", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "assent", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Normally, disciplinary action begins with a ____ warning for the first offense.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "verbal", "Opt_4": "legitimate", "Answer": "verbal", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_4_def": "correct; allowed"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is a lively ____ in the country at the moment on whether cannabis should be made legal or not.", "Opt_1": "prospect", "Opt_2": "debate", "Opt_3": "growth", "Opt_4": "treatment", "Answer": "debate", "Opt_1_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_2_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_3_def": "development, increase", "Opt_4_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You will ____ the carpet if you come inside with those dirty shoes.", "Opt_1": "forego", "Opt_2": "contact", "Opt_3": "ruin", "Opt_4": "prevent", "Answer": "ruin", "Opt_1_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_2_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_4_def": "to stop from doing or happening"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Asia is our closest region and essentially I feel that we need more understanding and ____ culturally to make sense of where we all are'.", "Opt_1": "broadcast", "Opt_2": "recover", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "regulate", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_2_def": "to get back", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to control"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you change your ____ or place of study, please amend your log-in details accordingly.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "label", "Opt_3": "discern", "Opt_4": "alter", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Aycock stated that he had looked over the horse before the ____ and did not observe any marks indicating that the horse had been cut.", "Opt_1": "manifest", "Opt_2": "define", "Opt_3": "expel", "Opt_4": "purchase", "Answer": "purchase", "Opt_1_def": "show", "Opt_2_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_3_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_4_def": "to buy"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The committee expects that as NOAA moves forward it will have to revise the plan on a ____ basis to incorporate new understanding.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "regular", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Typical conversations involve a huge amount of \"world knowledge\" or common facts about life which humans ____ as they grow.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "alter", "Opt_4": "conclude", "Answer": "accumulate", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to finish; to make a judgment"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I prefer to believe that the quality of my thinking has not diminished; I ____ have chosen a different format to express my ideas.", "Opt_1": "hence", "Opt_2": "conversely", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_2_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She will ____ reduce her chances of success if she continues to drink so much.", "Opt_1": "perhaps", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "universally", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "all over the world; by everyone"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A popular kind of literature these days is about the lives of ____ people who are caught up in extra____ events such as war or terrorism.", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "profound", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Board may presume that those actions created a ____ or abusive work environment which harms the efficiency of the service.", "Opt_1": "major", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "typical", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "hostile", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "usual", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is only one error in your writing. You put: He play tennis ____ of He plays tennis.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This ____ that you will be able to add money from your bank account to your StanfordCardPlan using this new online service.", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "behalf", "Opt_3": "aid", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_3_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She will ____ her chances of attending university if she doesn't start working harder.", "Opt_1": "expel", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "destroy", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "destroy", "Opt_1_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Our very ____ makes us aware of our need to do the utmost toward improving the situation of our not-so-fortunate neighbors.", "Opt_1": "privilege", "Opt_2": "issue", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "site", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_2_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "place"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The most ____ reason for her poor test scores is that she didn't prepare herself well enough.", "Opt_1": "liable", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Venus will next ____ in the night sky in August 2007.", "Opt_1": "appear", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "drain", "Opt_4": "denote", "Answer": "appear", "Opt_1_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You must try to ____ a balance between work and play. At the moment it's too much play!", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "share", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "achieve", "Answer": "achieve", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian region have in common ____ being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government has made overall ____ towards its goal of reducing child poverty.", "Opt_1": "progress", "Opt_2": "education", "Opt_3": "aid", "Opt_4": "mixture", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_2_def": "schooling", "Opt_3_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_4_def": "combination"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The writer clearly did not perform the experiment, but gave us what her very great ____ expected would happen.", "Opt_1": "directions", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "impact", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "instructions", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "On the back of this form or on a separate sheet, write a thorough ____ describing yourself, your interests, and why you have applied.", "Opt_1": "instruction", "Opt_2": "detail", "Opt_3": "mixture", "Opt_4": "statement", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_3_def": "combination", "Opt_4_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Worse yet, 1992 was no anomaly but the culmination of bad trends, most of them directly related to the company's ____ of focus.", "Opt_1": "propensity", "Opt_2": "expert", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_2_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "New challenges, opportunities, and demands are necessary to ensure that creativity and motivation do not ____ away.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "fulfill", "Opt_3": "fade", "Opt_4": "purchase", "Answer": "fade", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_4_def": "to buy"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Listening to the people is an ____ aspect of good government.", "Opt_1": "rare", "Opt_2": "proper", "Opt_3": "intrinsic", "Opt_4": "similar", "Answer": "intrinsic", "Opt_1_def": "unusual", "Opt_2_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_3_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_4_def": "like, almost the same as"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Almost all of the world's countries ____ to the United Nations organization.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "belong", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "belong", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Even with support, because of his health and limits on the hours he could work, he was unable to fulfill the duties of the ____ teaching job.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "confident", "Opt_3": "typical", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "typical", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_3_def": "usual", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "How did you decide that some items were ____ necessary?", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ family is expected to drive past the school tomorrow morning. The children will be standing by the road waving flags.", "Opt_1": "exact", "Opt_2": "arbitrary", "Opt_3": "adjacent", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "royal", "Opt_1_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_2_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_3_def": "next to", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The work involves some lifting and bending, and ____ requires travel away from the normal duty station.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "moreover", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_4_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ resulted in a statistic that did not seem correct.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Over the same period research was unable to measure ____ effects on achievement from readily available school characteristics.", "Opt_1": "broad", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "outstanding", "Opt_4": "significant", "Answer": "significant", "Opt_1_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "excellent", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school plans to ____ a list of the local doctors who can speak English.", "Opt_1": "allocate", "Opt_2": "compile", "Opt_3": "verify", "Opt_4": "destroy", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_2_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_3_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_4_def": "to break or damage completely"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The OCC provides counsel and legal advice in the development of policy, procedures, and ____ related to the management and operation of the UC Riverside campus.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "guarantee", "Answer": "strategy", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "How can you tell if the book, article, website, or other ____ you located is a valid, credible source?", "Opt_1": "portion", "Opt_2": "resource", "Opt_3": "substitute", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "resource", "Opt_1_def": "part, amount", "Opt_2_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_3_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The profession of social work is based on the values of service, social and economic justice, dignity and ____ of the person, importance of human relationships, and integrity and competence in practice.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A significant ____ to setting up a new business is the enormous amount of documentation that has to be completed.", "Opt_1": "obstacle", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "power", "Answer": "obstacle", "Opt_1_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "the right or authority to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Unlike other animals, humans have no ____ for survival; we often choose to do things that may be detrimental to our health.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "feature", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The organization has published a ____ of its history since it was founded in 1965.", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "pattern", "Opt_4": "debate", "Answer": "summary", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "formal discussion"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school plans to ____ a list of the local doctors who can speak English.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "install", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "allocate", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to give to (to promise to give)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "These projects will ____ student learning through the provision of modern technologies.", "Opt_1": "stress", "Opt_2": "enhance", "Opt_3": "refer", "Opt_4": "verify", "Answer": "enhance", "Opt_1_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_2_def": "to make something better", "Opt_3_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_4_def": "to prove or claim the truth"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In this section of the course, we cover less familiar territory, ____ the equations of relativistic acceleration.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A popular type of TV programme shows people who escape the ____ world and pretend to live as farmers did 100 years ago.", "Opt_1": "profound", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "temporary", "Answer": "contemporary", "Opt_1_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "for a short or limited time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The student said that his dog had eaten his homework. The teacher did not believe him but could not ____ what he said.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "refute", "Opt_4": "contain", "Answer": "refute", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to hold inside"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I think the students enjoy the fact that they have the ____ to try different things, says Harris. You can ask them to expand and see which direction they take.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "feature", "Opt_3": "tradition", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "liberty", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_3_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There have been several reviews done regarding the ____ of online course delivery tools that are on the market today.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "supply", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "comparison", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "provision, store", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It's not easy to ____ yourself when you're not going out and actually preparing for an opponent.", "Opt_1": "release", "Opt_2": "entitle", "Opt_3": "motivate", "Opt_4": "succeed", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_2_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to do well"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The method of evaluation used will be determined by the instructor but will generally include a combination (or all) of the following: homework, quizzes, exams, and a ____ final exam.", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "invisible", "Opt_4": "comprehensive", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_4_def": "full, complete"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A typical problem is that many companies will only employ workers with ____, but how do young people gain that ____ if they are not given a job. This is called a \"vicious circle\".", "Opt_1": "delay", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "lateness", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A significant ____ indicated that they enjoyed learning the course.", "Opt_1": "symptom", "Opt_2": "majority", "Opt_3": "sector", "Opt_4": "duty", "Answer": "majority", "Opt_1_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_2_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_3_def": "part; area", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Telephone and telegraph ____ from the Greek words meaning far speak and far write.", "Opt_1": "inhibit", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "decline", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The trial court noted that the newspaper articles ____ reported events and provided no editorial comment.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "furthermore", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to ____ changes on the earth beneath them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "remain", "Opt_3": "establish", "Opt_4": "propose", "Answer": "observe", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_3_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most people ____ to drive to huge out-of-town stores than use their local shops which are often much more expensive.", "Opt_1": "recognize", "Opt_2": "prefer", "Opt_3": "impose", "Opt_4": "suppose", "Answer": "prefer", "Opt_1_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_2_def": "to like better", "Opt_3_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to think, imagine"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This week's anniversary of the US-led war against Iraq is an appropriate ____ to ask: Are Americans safer than we were a year ago?", "Opt_1": "period", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "shift", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "occasion", "Opt_1_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "change", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You need to ____ a little more on the books that you read. It's not enough to just write what happens.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "examine", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The latest ____ of his bad behaviour was to lock another student in the toilet.", "Opt_1": "operation", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government has set a clear ____ on how much pollution factories are allowed to release into the atmosphere every year.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "facilities", "Opt_4": "limit", "Answer": "limit", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_4_def": "extent, boundary"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You have made excellent ____ in English this year. You will soon no longer need to take ESL lessons.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "task", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "job", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Describe the study in detail sufficient to convince the reviewer that the problem is ____ investigation.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The method of evaluation used will be determined by the instructor but will generally ____ a combination (or all) of the following: homework, quizzes, exams, and a comprehensive final exam.", "Opt_1": "undertake", "Opt_2": "include", "Opt_3": "magnify", "Opt_4": "commit", "Answer": "include", "Opt_1_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_2_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_3_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_4_def": "to do (often an offense)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The unpleasant ____ in the computer lab is sure to occupy my thoughts in the next few days.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "incident", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "dimension", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "happening; event", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "importance; amount"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The many hours of practice that usually underlie exceptional performance ____ out of sight to the casual observer.", "Opt_1": "regard", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "express", "Opt_4": "remain", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to stay; still exist"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Doctors are ____ encouraged by the reduction in the numbers of young people starting to smoke.", "Opt_1": "thereby", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "respectively", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "by doing this", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The different religious groups gradually came to realize that none of them could hope to ____ over all the others.", "Opt_1": "prevail", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "provoke", "Opt_4": "belong", "Answer": "prevail", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In 2000, over seventy percent of India's population, and ____ three quarters of its poor, lived in rural areas.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Including future irrelevant costs generally will not lead to a poor choice; it will only ____ the analysis.", "Opt_1": "justify", "Opt_2": "examine", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "verify", "Answer": "complicate", "Opt_1_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to prove or claim the truth"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In closing, I want to ____ that I know that our community is up to meeting these challenges and I know that the bold and inspiring decisions that will be made.", "Opt_1": "assert", "Opt_2": "control", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "omit", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to leave something out or not do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Check your ____ to be sure that class times do not overlap.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "concern", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The more information a sentence carries, the more it needs an ____ pattern that the reader can follow.", "Opt_1": "evident", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "compatible", "Opt_4": "pure", "Answer": "evident", "Opt_1_def": "clear", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_4_def": "complete, 100%"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The students decided to ____ in their attempt to fight bullying in the school.", "Opt_1": "monitor", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "unite", "Opt_4": "expand", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has passed laws to give equal rights to minority groups, but it can do nothing to remove the ____ that exists inside some people's heads.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "scale", "Opt_3": "function", "Opt_4": "behalf", "Answer": "prejudice", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "extent", "Opt_3_def": "job or role", "Opt_4_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Great Britain, Canada, and the United States do not intend to ____ the secret until means have been found to control the bomb.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "mention", "Opt_3": "focus", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "reveal", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to say; state", "Opt_3_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A half century ago the conflict over ____ regulation of railroads was the chief issue in Alabama politics.", "Opt_1": "state", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "event", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "a happening", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Next year the school will ____ a policy of no smoking on campus for both teachers and students.", "Opt_1": "arrange", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "refer", "Opt_4": "implement", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_4_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The Birth Control Pill may have modernized society, but it tore ____ a nation and created many social problems that did not exist before its invention.", "Opt_1": "convenient", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In most countries of the world you need to get a ____ before you can drive a car.", "Opt_1": "grant", "Opt_2": "incentive", "Opt_3": "error", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "license", "Opt_1_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_2_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a mistake", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Lincoln, while receiving a majority vote ____ northerners, did not receive a majority of ALL the popular votes.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A willingness to question what you are told is ____ to the best students.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "relevant", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "intrinsic", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian region have in common ____ being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is less widely recognized, moreover, that growth and globalization also ____ to accelerate environmental damage.", "Opt_1": "store", "Opt_2": "attain", "Opt_3": "refuse", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_2_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The most logical reason for her poor test scores is that she didn't ____ herself well enough.", "Opt_1": "trust", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "deteriorate", "Opt_4": "prepare", "Answer": "prepare", "Opt_1_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to ____ a limit on the number of solutions searched for, since in general the number of such solutions could be infinite.", "Opt_1": "impose", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "compete", "Opt_4": "include", "Answer": "impose", "Opt_1_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to put in; to have in"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Why did the Bush Administration refuse to modify its goals in ____ to achieve a consensus?", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "penalty", "Opt_3": "support", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_3_def": "help", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It was not the ____ of this book to discuss whether America can win the war, or whether it must lose it.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "point", "Answer": "goal", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "purpose; reason; value"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Employees interested in participating in a ____ tax sheltered annuity program should contact their personnel officer.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "voluntary", "Opt_3": "original", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_3_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I don't think that the school's ____ of the students caught smoking in the toilets was very fair.", "Opt_1": "status", "Opt_2": "sequence", "Opt_3": "treatment", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "position, standing", "Opt_2_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_3_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Even though you may know your housemates well, you should always take the ____ to lock the door. Windows should also be secured.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "expert", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "But mine was not a ____ Negro family. My grandmother never took in washing or worked in service or went much to church.", "Opt_1": "typical", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "typical", "Opt_1_def": "usual", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you are in constant pain you should ____ a doctor.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "warn", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This has been the province of scientists and engineers for many years and has only ____ been considered a hot research topic with real business potential.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This piece of work is much ____ to your last one. I'm glad to see you are getting better.", "Opt_1": "superior", "Opt_2": "broad", "Opt_3": "tough", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "superior", "Opt_1_def": "better", "Opt_2_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The information that you receive in today's lesson will ____ you to complete your project on nuclear energy.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "defend", "Opt_3": "enable", "Opt_4": "reverse", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_3_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to turn back or go back"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school is working on a ____ to give all students a portable computer for use in lessons.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "function", "Opt_3": "tradition", "Opt_4": "scheme", "Answer": "scheme", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "job or role", "Opt_3_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_4_def": "plan. idea, project"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We have had no chance to examine changes of this sort systematically, but ____ offer them as examples of processes that we expect to be completed.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "But it is not a substitute for ____ food safety programs throughout the food distribution system.", "Opt_1": "comprehensive", "Opt_2": "radical", "Opt_3": "rigid", "Opt_4": "available", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "full, complete", "Opt_2_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_3_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_4_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Further analysis suggested that the ____ was worse for women than men.", "Opt_1": "outcome", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "mixture", "Answer": "outcome", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "combination"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "While its lack of clarity was seen by some early critics as a clear ____ of error and confusion, it was seen by others as a hallmark of genius.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "lecture", "Opt_3": "symptom", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "symptom", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Demonstrators tried to ____ the opening of the new airport runway.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "degenerate", "Opt_3": "declare", "Opt_4": "frustrate", "Answer": "frustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to state", "Opt_4_def": "to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is important to ____ language that reinforces the dominant culture's attitude to disability.", "Opt_1": "review", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "force", "Answer": "review", "Opt_1_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Catherwood Library is the most ____ resource of its type in North America.", "Opt_1": "profound", "Opt_2": "radical", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "rapid", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_2_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "quick"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "His advice was to ____ short-term temptation when investing in stocks.", "Opt_1": "devise", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "resist", "Answer": "resist", "Opt_1_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to fight against"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is an ____ for a politician to be able to give a clear but concise statement of what he or she believes in.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "profession", "Opt_4": "area", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_4_def": "field, sphere"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The rat lungworm, is the ____ cause of eosinophilic meningitis worldwide.", "Opt_1": "ambiguous", "Opt_2": "principal", "Opt_3": "ancient", "Opt_4": "abstract", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "very old", "Opt_4_def": "not specific or concrete"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is much effort being expended on attempting to ____ this problem.", "Opt_1": "destroy", "Opt_2": "decrease", "Opt_3": "trigger", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "solve", "Opt_1_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The author had failed to ____ his report, so it was impossible to check the truth of his claims.", "Opt_1": "resign", "Opt_2": "enlarge", "Opt_3": "suggest", "Opt_4": "annotate", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_2_def": "to make larger", "Opt_3_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_4_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The nine women here say the poor treatment of ____ workers is an apartheid-era relic that has no place in democratic South Africa.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "sole", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "domestic", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "only", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Major Smith occupied the city as ordered but was unable to ____ the bridge, lacking both a drill and powder.", "Opt_1": "destroy", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "establish", "Opt_4": "clarify", "Answer": "destroy", "Opt_1_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_4_def": "to make something clear, explain"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most historians agree that Kievan Russia was not a ____ political, cultural, or ethnic entity.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "contemporary", "Opt_4": "adequate", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_4_def": "good enough; ok"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Another ____ meaning of due is the date on something has to be done, as in Don't forget. Your project is due tomorrow.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "feasible", "Opt_3": "radical", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "common", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "possible", "Opt_3_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The minister gave an ____ answer when asked if the government intended to raise taxes.", "Opt_1": "drastic", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "severe", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "severe; great", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "serious, harsh"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Each programme is designed to give students the opportunity to ____ significant social, political and environmental issues using an innovative comparative model.", "Opt_1": "explore", "Opt_2": "impose", "Opt_3": "withdraw", "Opt_4": "overcome", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_2_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_4_def": "to conquer, defeat"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You can't always control what happens to you, but you can always control how you ____ to what happens to you.", "Opt_1": "react", "Opt_2": "pursue", "Opt_3": "entitle", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "react", "Opt_1_def": "to respond", "Opt_2_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_3_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Due to its association with the churches and schools, the Samoan language enjoyed high ____ in Tokelau for a long time.", "Opt_1": "generation", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "status", "Answer": "prestige", "Opt_1_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "position, standing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to ____ force in order to achieve peace in a troubled region.", "Opt_1": "demonstrate", "Opt_2": "undergo", "Opt_3": "acknowledge", "Opt_4": "exert", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The most ____ reason for her poor test scores is that she didn't prepare herself well enough.", "Opt_1": "external", "Opt_2": "logical", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "outside", "Opt_2_def": "making sense", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Children who have no ____ to their behaviour are often unhappy.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "method", "Opt_4": "point", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "purpose; reason; value"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The best ____ is to change the nutrient solution every week instead of every two weeks.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "trace", "Opt_3": "goal", "Opt_4": "remedy", "Answer": "remedy", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_3_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_4_def": "cure (often for an illness)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The new Smartboard in my classroom must ____ a lot of energy. I've already had to change the bulb 3 times.", "Opt_1": "detect", "Opt_2": "consume", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "enforce", "Answer": "consume", "Opt_1_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_2_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The difference between Japanese and Korean prices ____ decreased until virtually zero where it has remained over the past few years.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "European democratic nation states have increasingly lost influence over the ____ of their own economies.", "Opt_1": "investigate", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "control", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "conduct", "Opt_1_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is usually easy for teachers to ____ if an ESL student has copied text from a webpage.", "Opt_1": "destroy", "Opt_2": "commit", "Opt_3": "discern", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "discern", "Opt_1_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_2_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We have a painting at home that's very valuable. It must be ____ more than a million dollars!", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The management wanted to dismiss the incompetent employee but could find no-one better to ____ him.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "govern", "Opt_3": "replace", "Opt_4": "contradict", "Answer": "replace", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_3_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This section is not an alternative to reading course materials or attending lectures, but rather an opportunity ____ topics in greater detail.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "exert", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The men searched the entire camp, digging ____ the snow and even into the earth, but no paper was found, no diaries and no documents.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "On the whole the great ____ of Canadian immigration of the past generation has been drawn from the English-speaking countries.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "gain", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Sometimes it is ____ to exert force in order to achieve peace in a troubled region.", "Opt_1": "immediate", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "necessary", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "necessary", "Opt_1_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A headache may seem like a ____ problem, but it could be the sign of something more serious.", "Opt_1": "political", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "trivial", "Opt_1_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Ultimately, this research will lessen the negative health impact of the hurricanes, which in turn will lessen the ____ burden on society.", "Opt_1": "crucial", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "extremely important", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There have been several reviews done regarding the ____ of online course delivery tools that are on the market today.", "Opt_1": "background", "Opt_2": "comparison", "Opt_3": "fallacy", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "comparison", "Opt_1_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_3_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Individuals should report the ____ to a faculty or staff member at the university with whom they are comfortable.", "Opt_1": "incident", "Opt_2": "section", "Opt_3": "community", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "happening; event", "Opt_2_def": "part", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Older people should have a ____ check-up at the doctors at least once a year.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "thorough", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Our teachers ____ the school's philosophy that only excellence is good enough.", "Opt_1": "strain", "Opt_2": "enumerate", "Opt_3": "gather", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to list", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not the only method of teaching we use at the university; ____ we calibrate our teaching techniques to fit our abilities.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This validation will ____ him/her as a \"special student\" and will entitle him/her to the use of additional university facilities, such as the union building and the gym, and to free admissions for selected lectures.", "Opt_1": "revive", "Opt_2": "abuse", "Opt_3": "identify", "Opt_4": "select", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_2_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_3_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_4_def": "to choose"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Not many people will change their habits or lifestyle ____ because a government minister tells them it's a good idea.", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Your supervisor has been provided with the above information and should be able to ____ any questions you may have.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "demonstrate", "Opt_3": "clarify", "Opt_4": "remain", "Answer": "clarify", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_4_def": "to stay; still exist"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Our ____ provides professional development in the field of DNA sequencing and genomics for graduates.", "Opt_1": "summary", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "reply", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "an answer", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Given the abundance of oxygen and silicon in the crust, it should not be surprising that the most ____ minerals in the earth's crust are the silicates.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "abundant", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "abundant", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "common"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "World leaders met in Bali to discuss global warming. Many people say that the whole ____ was a waste of time and money.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "asset", "Opt_3": "affair", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "affair", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Rules do not usually ____ creativity or passion; rather they demand conformity and make us fear change.", "Opt_1": "avoid", "Opt_2": "retain", "Opt_3": "stimulate", "Opt_4": "encounter", "Answer": "stimulate", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_4_def": "to meet or experience"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The head teacher is thinking of introducing a school uniform. Most students are ____ the idea.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The price of a raw material for a production process may be reduced if a sufficiently large ____ is purchased at each inventory replenishment.", "Opt_1": "programme", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "cause", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "the reason why something happens"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It was given to the grandmother by her grandfather in 1852, when the ____ was a member of the California assembly.", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "latter", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The quality of your work has improved ____ in the last few weeks.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The current generation of children is usually thought to be less polite and hard-working than the ____ one.", "Opt_1": "previous", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "forthcoming", "Answer": "previous", "Opt_1_def": "the one before", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "coming soon"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "What is the next letter in the ____ O, T, F, S, N, E, _?", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "sequence", "Opt_3": "legislation", "Opt_4": "constraint", "Answer": "sequence", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_3_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to prevent"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Instead of quick results, Cronbach (1963) believed that consistent experiences ____ improve performance over time.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "namely", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Calderone's insistence that sex education should begin as early as kindergarten did not ____ religious conservative groups.", "Opt_1": "subsidize", "Opt_2": "impress", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "unite", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to support financially", "Opt_2_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is not always easy for teachers to differentiate poor work that is ____ to laziness and poor work that is ____ to inability.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We had disagreed strongly over politics before, and while these arguments did not ____ our friendship in the least, I wished to avoid potential conflict.", "Opt_1": "strain", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "behave", "Opt_4": "eliminate", "Answer": "strain", "Opt_1_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to dispose of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She has a ____ in one eye that makes it difficult for her to read from the board.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "ratio", "Opt_3": "statement", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "defect", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_3_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The two procedures consistently showed that garlic did not inhibit the ____ of oral bacteria.", "Opt_1": "mechanism", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "growth", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "development, increase"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This program will ____ entry to the field and to advanced study of nutrition.", "Opt_1": "create", "Opt_2": "accelerate", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "culminate", "Answer": "accelerate", "Opt_1_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_2_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to end"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Parents who ____ their children were often ____ed themselves.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "improve", "Opt_4": "neglect", "Answer": "neglect", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to not think about or care for"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some politicians ____ that too much immigration will result in fewer jobs for the people born in the country.", "Opt_1": "admit", "Opt_2": "fear", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "reflect", "Answer": "fear", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_2_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to think or consider"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ was unclear. It had been hand-drawn and then copied using weak ink.", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "skill", "Opt_3": "diagram", "Opt_4": "category", "Answer": "diagram", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_3_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_4_def": "group of similar items"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school had to pay a small ____ to the parents of the boy who hurt his arm on the ski trip.", "Opt_1": "area", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "fault", "Opt_4": "choice", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_4_def": "decision, selection"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is a well-known fact that smoking is a ____ of lung cancer.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "citizen", "Opt_4": "cause", "Answer": "cause", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_4_def": "the reason why something happens"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "His lungs were filled in an ____ with a great volume of driven air which he could not expel.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "radical", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "instant", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "immediate"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Fire Chief Anthony Yenzer said the ____ cause of the fire was determined shortly afterwards through interviews with the two male students.", "Opt_1": "chief", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "novel", "Opt_4": "regular", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "new", "Opt_4_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Now retired and free to speak out about the scandal, Karpinski is devoting herself to publicizing her ____ of event.", "Opt_1": "fragment", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "version", "Opt_1_def": "part of something", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school plans to ____ \ufffd\ufffd10,000 to buy new computers next year for the science lab.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "evolve", "Opt_4": "allocate", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_4_def": "to give to (to promise to give)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Factory farming is just not ____ with animal welfare.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "eligible", "Opt_3": "compatible", "Opt_4": "concise", "Answer": "compatible", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_3_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_4_def": "short, not detailed"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The head teacher is thinking of introducing a school uniform. Most students are ____ the idea.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He flew in with 500 rolls of film and 1400 pounds of provisions but forgot to ____ for the pilot to pick him up again.", "Opt_1": "admit", "Opt_2": "arrange", "Opt_3": "establish", "Opt_4": "train", "Answer": "arrange", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_2_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_3_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_4_def": "to teach someone how to do a job"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If he is correct this would certainly be an ____ solution to an ancient problem.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "elementary", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "apparent", "Answer": "elementary", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "clear; obvious"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government is planning to spend a ____ amount of money on new hospitals next year.", "Opt_1": "preliminary", "Opt_2": "substantial", "Opt_3": "hostile", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "substantial", "Opt_1_def": "first; initial", "Opt_2_def": "large", "Opt_3_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some steps you can take to ____ yourself and your property are: Lock your room when sleeping and when you leave your room.", "Opt_1": "expel", "Opt_2": "protect", "Opt_3": "assure", "Opt_4": "suffer", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_2_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_4_def": "to experience something bad or painful"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The union was not able to ____ all of its goals in this budget session.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "accomplish", "Opt_3": "acknowledge", "Opt_4": "appoint", "Answer": "accomplish", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Global warming seems ____ to increase unless we can find greener ways of producing energy.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "adequate", "Opt_3": "adjacent", "Opt_4": "certain", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_3_def": "next to", "Opt_4_def": "sure"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Calderone's insistence that sex education should begin as early as kindergarten did not ____ religious conservative groups.", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "inhibit", "Opt_3": "impress", "Opt_4": "propose", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you ____ the globe by 360\ufffdX, you will return to your starting point.", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "overcome", "Opt_3": "alter", "Opt_4": "neglect", "Answer": "rotate", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to not think about or care for"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The best remedy is to change the nutrient solution every week ____ of every two weeks.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He seems to be lacking the ____ to improve his rather poor grades.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "objective", "Opt_4": "layer", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_4_def": "level"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is not enough to ____ children not to play with fireworks. It should be illegal for children to buy them.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "trigger", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "deduce", "Answer": "warn", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He started searching for evidence of Wilson's existence and ____ succeeded in documenting her life up to 1863.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian region have in common ____ being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A concise and informative email subject line is very helpful, whereas one that is too ____ or too long can get your email mistaken for something unimportant.", "Opt_1": "political", "Opt_2": "tough", "Opt_3": "main", "Opt_4": "vague", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is an advantage for a politician to be able to give a clear but concise ____ of what he or she believes in.", "Opt_1": "statement", "Opt_2": "vary", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_2_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Tests are valid when they ____ what they claim to ____, and reliable when they ____ consistently.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "inhibit", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "measure", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Our focus is to ____ each student to achieve their full potential as they strive for success in our five cornerstones of Academic Excellence.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "denote", "Opt_3": "address", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In many cases, ____ stating to the student that the behavior is unacceptable and must not occur again is sufficient.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to first ____ all possibilities for Federal and state financial aid programs before seeking alternative loans.", "Opt_1": "appeal", "Opt_2": "fare", "Opt_3": "reverse", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "exhaust", "Opt_1_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_2_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_3_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Not everyone is ____ enough to have internet access at home.", "Opt_1": "novel", "Opt_2": "credible", "Opt_3": "royal", "Opt_4": "fortunate", "Answer": "fortunate", "Opt_1_def": "new", "Opt_2_def": "believable", "Opt_3_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_4_def": "lucky"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some students will ____ that advertising does not \"mean\" anything; they may feel that ads have little effect on the way people think and act.", "Opt_1": "insist", "Opt_2": "transfer", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_2_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I'm not sure how to define any of these ____ terms, and yet I recognize some of the components of forgiveness.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "abstract", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "abstract", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_4_def": "large"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If breastfeeding is not possible, ____ infant milk formulas are a good alternative.", "Opt_1": "anonymous", "Opt_2": "commercial", "Opt_3": "certain", "Opt_4": "discrete", "Answer": "commercial", "Opt_1_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_2_def": "to do with business", "Opt_3_def": "sure", "Opt_4_def": "separate"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some people think that the ____ way to stop people smoking is to raise the price of cigarettes sky-high.", "Opt_1": "ambiguous", "Opt_2": "ideal", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "ideal", "Opt_1_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_2_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you ____ a student of plagiarism, you must have strong evidence.", "Opt_1": "accuse", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "dominate", "Opt_4": "appear", "Answer": "accuse", "Opt_1_def": "to blame", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_4_def": "to come, be seen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The idea was to remove the possibility of a ____ court or government treating a foreign investor unfairly.", "Opt_1": "valid", "Opt_2": "local", "Opt_3": "widespread", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "correct", "Opt_2_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_3_def": "common", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has some loose plans to reduce ____ tax in the next 5 years.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many people believe that the government made a huge mistake in invading Iraq, and ____ that they lied about the reasons.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "moreover", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "moreover", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It was only one stage in a long struggle that did not come to a ____ end until 1971.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "legal", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "spontaneous", "Answer": "legal", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "happening without warning or planning"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It took him a ____ time to finish the project.", "Opt_1": "legitimate", "Opt_2": "massive", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "pure", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "complete, 100%"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This also helps you ____ which variables it is essential to control to avoid an ambiguous answer.", "Opt_1": "incorporate", "Opt_2": "arise", "Opt_3": "determine", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "determine", "Opt_1_def": "to include", "Opt_2_def": "to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Students who are awarded an International Student Scholarship must ____ the following requirements each semester in order to continue receiving this award.", "Opt_1": "solve", "Opt_2": "remain", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "prove", "Answer": "fulfill", "Opt_1_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_2_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to show to be true"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She came to school yesterday ____ feeling very unwell.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government minister expressed regret at her thoughtless ____ about 'lazy incompetent teachers'.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "comment", "Opt_3": "property", "Opt_4": "guide", "Answer": "comment", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_3_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_4_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "\"Helpless in the face of terrorism\" - that's not a ____ that University of Cincinnati geography", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "phrase", "Opt_3": "education", "Opt_4": "gap", "Answer": "phrase", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_3_def": "schooling", "Opt_4_def": "space, opening or time between"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Never has the ____ of a stable, prosperous, and democratic hemisphere seemed so close within reach.", "Opt_1": "staff", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "situation", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "circumstances"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is ____ that you try to increase your English academic vocabulary. And the best way to do this is by lots of reading of non-fiction.", "Opt_1": "essential", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "scarce", "Opt_4": "valid", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_4_def": "correct"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You can submit your work at any time ____ to the due date.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "\"Recommended Changes to Student Handbook\" was the next ____ for discussion.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "potential", "Opt_4": "aspect", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "good possibility", "Opt_4_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain."}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is essential that governments take ____ before making the decision to go to war.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "constraint", "Opt_3": "property", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_3_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You will not get a ____ reply to your email. He is very busy at the moment.", "Opt_1": "prompt", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "sufficient", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "prompt", "Opt_1_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "enough", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In August, UMBC will ____ a new home page on our Web site.", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "verify", "Opt_3": "launch", "Opt_4": "stimulate", "Answer": "launch", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_3_def": "to begin", "Opt_4_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government claims that it invaded Iraq to bring democracy to that country. Many people, however, claim that this is not a ____ reason to go to war.", "Opt_1": "preliminary", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "sufficient", "Opt_4": "valid", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "first; initial", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "enough", "Opt_4_def": "correct"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ was first observed in 1911 by Onnes, who noted that the resistance of a frozen mercury rod abruptly dropped to zero.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "facilities", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "assignment", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "a task; the giving of a task"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Scientists have found life over a mile below the ____ of the sea, far from the sun.", "Opt_1": "surface", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "statement", "Answer": "surface", "Opt_1_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The case of Nicaragua demonstrates how the United States failed to ____ on the implementation of democratic procedures.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "announce", "Opt_3": "depart", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_3_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Bush administration will not back down on pursuing new sanctions against Iran over its nuclear program ____ questions about their effectiveness.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "To develop a comprehensive approach to business, managers must ____ the strengths of their employees in assigning tasks.", "Opt_1": "culminate", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "propose", "Opt_4": "utilize", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to end", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The researchers found that some of the key decision makers lacked the ____ knowledge and expertise to handle the disaster.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "fortunate", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "lucky"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many of the faculty and students we talked with wanted to remain ____ and asked that they not be listed by name in our report.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "anonymous", "Opt_3": "familiar", "Opt_4": "constant", "Answer": "anonymous", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_3_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; long-lasting"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Do not ____ the period after an abbreviation such as in. (for inch), which could be confused with the word in.", "Opt_1": "omit", "Opt_2": "exclude", "Opt_3": "halt", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "omit", "Opt_1_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_2_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There will be a ____ class after school today for those who want extra practice for the test.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "secure", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "medium", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "safe", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "in the middle"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is hardly a surprise that national governments have failed to solve global problems, since they have also failed to solve their own ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "domestic", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Many Western businesses are finding it difficult to ____ with Asian companies which pay their workers far less money.", "Opt_1": "provoke", "Opt_2": "attend", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and therefore not ____ considering.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Throughout the day, with a brief interval for lunch, he stared at the history project which was ____ the next morning.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is ____ that increases in short sale transactions precede stock price declines.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "evidence", "Opt_3": "level", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_3_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Given the abundance of oxygen and silicon in the crust, it should not be surprising that the most ____ minerals in the earth's crust are the silicates.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "annual", "Opt_4": "medium", "Answer": "abundant", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "yearly", "Opt_4_def": "in the middle"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and therefore not ____ considering.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is not the only method of teaching we use at the university; ____ we calibrate our teaching techniques to fit our abilities.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You have learned this lesson that water and other liquids ____ sound better than air.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "expand", "Opt_3": "engage", "Opt_4": "transmit", "Answer": "transmit", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_3_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_4_def": "to send or convey"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Your low grades will ____ you of the chance of taking part in sports trips.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "predict", "Opt_4": "deprive", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_4_def": "to take away (the opportunity)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Turkish law requires foreign scholars to ____ formal permission to carry out research at institutions in Turkey.", "Opt_1": "dispose", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "introduce", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The aim of the proposal is to ____ people of the liberty to download songs and videos from the internet.", "Opt_1": "modify", "Opt_2": "depend", "Opt_3": "dismiss", "Opt_4": "deprive", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_3_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_4_def": "to take away (the opportunity)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is ____ that you hand in the essay on time. If you don't, you will fail the course.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "crucial", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "extremely important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There are many things that people can do in the battle ____ global warming. For instance, they can turn off lights when they leave the room.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Roman Jewish population did not ____ during Sixtus' reign; indeed, there was always movement of Jews in and out of the region.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "deviate", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to be different", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The company directors invited the workers' union to ____ in a meeting to discuss the new factory.", "Opt_1": "appreciate", "Opt_2": "participate", "Opt_3": "elect", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "participate", "Opt_1_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_2_def": "to take part", "Opt_3_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Chelsea and Liverpool are ____ the 2nd and 3rd most successful football clubs.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "respectively", "Answer": "respectively", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "An analysis of the historical causes of slavery is ____ the scope of this course.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Not any of these persons shall perform or permit any practice that may ____ the reputation of the university.", "Opt_1": "proceed", "Opt_2": "emerge", "Opt_3": "terminate", "Opt_4": "damage", "Answer": "damage", "Opt_1_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_2_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_3_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "University staff will notice the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages ____ of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Howard has many chances to ____ into a better father and husband, but he fails to do so.", "Opt_1": "interrupt", "Opt_2": "exist", "Opt_3": "arrange", "Opt_4": "evolve", "Answer": "evolve", "Opt_1_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_3_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_4_def": "to develop (into something better)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You know that ____ of a law will not prevent you from being arrested for breaking it.", "Opt_1": "period", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "sector", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "part; area"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The opening of the new sports ____ was the biggest operation in the school's history.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "stimulate", "Opt_3": "commit", "Opt_4": "block", "Answer": "block", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_3_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_4_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is easy to ____ the government for its failures, but no-one has come up with any better ideas.", "Opt_1": "appreciate", "Opt_2": "construct", "Opt_3": "criticize", "Opt_4": "unite", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_2_def": "to make", "Opt_3_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is important for teachers to create a positive learning ____ in the classroom.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "truth", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "atmosphere", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many students who receive a grade lower than they want, do so because they fail to ____ their texts.", "Opt_1": "descend", "Opt_2": "exchange", "Opt_3": "annotate", "Opt_4": "revive", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_3_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to bring back (to life)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He has lost the desire to consider what is right and wrong because he was hurt, ____ devastated, when the love of his life disappeared.", "Opt_1": "thus", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "indeed", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "so", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some people say that there should be ____ schools for students who are not so interested in writing or learning from books.", "Opt_1": "key", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "spontaneous", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "technical", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The price of stamps will increase only if the total ____ of mail does not decrease and the postal service does not become more efficient.", "Opt_1": "strategy", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "volume", "Opt_1_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some students claim that they can ____ watch TV and do their homework.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "accordingly", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The most ____ reason for the bad test scores is that the teacher was new and inexperienced.", "Opt_1": "evident", "Opt_2": "familiar", "Opt_3": "probable", "Opt_4": "temporary", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "clear", "Opt_2_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_3_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_4_def": "for a short or limited time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Princeton University computer scientist Edward Felton has decided not to ____ a paper on how his research team broke the code of copyright protection.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "broadcast", "Opt_3": "prefer", "Opt_4": "publish", "Answer": "publish", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_3_def": "to like better", "Opt_4_def": "to make available in paper or online form"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The public are ____ satisfied with the government's performance.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "accordingly", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I am ____ of her problems at home, but this doesn't mean that she can be rude and disruptive in school.", "Opt_1": "credible", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "believable", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government was unable to ____ that it was considering invading North Korea.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "present", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "deny", "Answer": "deny", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "When the moisture con____s, heat is released into the air, making it warmer and less ____ than its surroundings.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "contemporary", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "dense", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school has a ____ of approximately one teacher for every fifteen students.", "Opt_1": "affair", "Opt_2": "ratio", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "attitude", "Answer": "ratio", "Opt_1_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "But his son, who had hoped to occupy the throne of Armenia, could not ____ his discontent.", "Opt_1": "conceal", "Opt_2": "conserve", "Opt_3": "judge", "Opt_4": "advise", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to hide", "Opt_2_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_3_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "People are more likely to take risks they would not take when sober, and are unable to judge accurately their ____ to drive.", "Opt_1": "standard", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "ability", "Opt_4": "magnitude", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "quality", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_4_def": "size; amount"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many Western businesses are finding it difficult to ____ with Asian companies which pay their workers far less money.", "Opt_1": "compete", "Opt_2": "seek", "Opt_3": "appear", "Opt_4": "fade", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_3_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_4_def": "to disappear slowly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The first section of this course is concerned with understanding the ____ concepts of design: How to analyze and talk about visual material.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "inevitable", "Opt_3": "smooth", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school will always ____ its policy of expelling students for repeated plagiarism.", "Opt_1": "edit", "Opt_2": "enlarge", "Opt_3": "enforce", "Opt_4": "connect", "Answer": "enforce", "Opt_1_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to make larger", "Opt_3_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or put together"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is during adolescence that clear gender differences arise which might ____ to the varying rates of depression.", "Opt_1": "praise", "Opt_2": "consume", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "highlight", "Answer": "contribute", "Opt_1_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_2_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to show (the important features of something)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Counselors will begin on-going sessions with a student only after having obtained signed ____ of the student and signed consent of the parent.", "Opt_1": "deal", "Opt_2": "gap", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "assent", "Answer": "assent", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The main ____ of this ESL course is to improve students' ability in academic writing.", "Opt_1": "background", "Opt_2": "authority", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "objective", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "aim or goal"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school tried to ____ the fact that one of its teachers had a criminal record.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "produce", "Opt_3": "invent", "Opt_4": "suppress", "Answer": "suppress", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to make or create", "Opt_3_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In proof of this, we may note that slavery did not ____ immediately on the reception of Christianity.", "Opt_1": "collapse", "Opt_2": "measure", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "cease", "Answer": "cease", "Opt_1_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_2_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We ____ his behavior as very serious and we hope this ban will serve as an example.If you violate the rules about downloading internet files, you will not be allowed to use the computer lab.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "appreciate", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "view", "Answer": "view", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to have an opinion"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The blue whale may be extinct by the end of the century unless we do all we can to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "conserve", "Opt_2": "regard", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "conserve", "Opt_1_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_2_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school's facilities have been improved ____ with the addition of a second library and media centre.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Thanks to the accurate description of the witnesses, the police were able to ____ the bank robbers.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "reverse", "Opt_3": "identify", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_3_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Fish farming is an ____ that should go some way to compensating for the reduction of fish in the oceans.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "loss", "Opt_4": "innovation", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_4_def": "new object or idea"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government took the ____ decision to decrease tax.", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "rational", "Opt_3": "main", "Opt_4": "complete", "Answer": "bold", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "full or finished"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The airport authorities have decided to ____ passengers to carry only very small amounts of liquid onto the plane.", "Opt_1": "commence", "Opt_2": "permit", "Opt_3": "cooperate", "Opt_4": "focus", "Answer": "permit", "Opt_1_def": "to start", "Opt_2_def": "to allow", "Opt_3_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_4_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Upon completion of the course, students will be able to discern how grammar and usage errors can ____ with meaning.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "discern", "Opt_4": "enumerate", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_4_def": "to list"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Our focus is to motivate each student to achieve their full potential as they ____ for success in our five cornerstones of Academic Excellence.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "deliver", "Opt_3": "strive", "Opt_4": "prefer", "Answer": "strive", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_3_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_4_def": "to like better"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Recent government IT initiatives focus narrowly on a specific technical problem, like enabling ____ data communication or Web-based transactions.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "competent", "Opt_4": "concise", "Answer": "mobile", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_4_def": "short, not detailed"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "My science teacher has a ____ knowledge of nuclear physics.", "Opt_1": "profound", "Opt_2": "related", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "profound", "Opt_1_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_2_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I cannot think of any ____ writers who are better than her.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "deficient", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "contemporary", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_4_def": "new"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "As a child, he began to stutter severely and, ____ the best efforts of his teachers and parents, he was unable to overcome it.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In the heat of election campaigning, it is in no-one's interest to impose an ____ crisis upon the economy.", "Opt_1": "various", "Opt_2": "artificial", "Opt_3": "ambitious", "Opt_4": "thorough", "Answer": "artificial", "Opt_1_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_2_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_3_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_4_def": "complete and careful"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There were complications with the pregnancy, so she had to ____ starting school for a semester.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There was also no apparent record of an attempt to measure the ____ between individual differences in facial shape.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "cause", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is ____ important that you establish a strong motive to return to your country after you complete your studies.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "extremely", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "very"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The revolutionary ____ must come from those basic human needs that are failed by capitalism.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "victory", "Opt_4": "impulse", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "win", "Opt_4_def": "reason or motivation to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some information is collected on our ____ by outside agencies in order to provide services to our visitors.", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "behalf", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is our belief that the students were not given a fair hearing, and ____ that the punishment was unjust.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "furthermore", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "furthermore", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is not always easy for teachers to differentiate ____ work that is due to laziness and ____ work that is due to inability.", "Opt_1": "initial", "Opt_2": "latter", "Opt_3": "global", "Opt_4": "poor", "Answer": "poor", "Opt_1_def": "starting, first", "Opt_2_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_3_def": "world", "Opt_4_def": "bad, unsatisfactory"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Our experiments with SRM 1010a led us to the conclusion that this was too subjective a ____ of evaluating results.", "Opt_1": "background", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "method", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "method", "Opt_1_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "People are more likely to migrate in times of war or ____ poverty.", "Opt_1": "relevant", "Opt_2": "adequate", "Opt_3": "classic", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_2_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_3_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Eat less, exercise more: the ____ for weight loss is so simple, yet so hard.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ answer is not at all straightforward, unless the uncertainty itself is related in a particular way to the passage of time.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "precise", "Opt_3": "odd", "Opt_4": "major", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "exact", "Opt_3_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The nurse gave me a ____ for my headache.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "quality", "Opt_3": "treatment", "Opt_4": "remedy", "Answer": "remedy", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "worth or value", "Opt_3_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_4_def": "cure (often for an illness)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Euro has taken on a ____ far greater than its economic substance.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "education", "Opt_3": "fund", "Opt_4": "dimension", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "schooling", "Opt_3_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_4_def": "importance; amount"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "For the first time, satellite imagery has allowed scientists to observe how icebergs in a remote corner of Antarctica can ____ an entire marine ecosystem.", "Opt_1": "disrupt", "Opt_2": "provoke", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "disrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_2_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you look at the course policies you will notice an ____ that accounts for 4% of your grade.", "Opt_1": "operation", "Opt_2": "attribute", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "item", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "thing, element"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He came up with a ____ excuse for not doing his homework, but his teacher did not believe him.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "novel", "Opt_3": "certain", "Opt_4": "vague", "Answer": "novel", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "new", "Opt_3_def": "sure", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you currently do not ____ the skill to meet this standard, you are advised to enroll in a class that will provide you with this capability.", "Opt_1": "isolate", "Opt_2": "possess", "Opt_3": "organize", "Opt_4": "deserve", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_2_def": "to have or own", "Opt_3_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_4_def": "to have the right to something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This project will ____ in a major research essay of 2000 words.", "Opt_1": "damage", "Opt_2": "appreciate", "Opt_3": "culminate", "Opt_4": "permit", "Answer": "culminate", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_3_def": "to end", "Opt_4_def": "to allow"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Where can I ____ about the teaching job I saw in the newspaper?", "Opt_1": "organize", "Opt_2": "inquire", "Opt_3": "diminish", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "inquire", "Opt_1_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_2_def": "to ask", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Thus, while we do not wish to ____ on future developments, we need to consider the actual and potential effects of the decision.", "Opt_1": "behave", "Opt_2": "speculate", "Opt_3": "retain", "Opt_4": "earn", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The contributors assert that teaching is a gendered occupation with low ____ and relatively low pay.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "circumstances", "Opt_3": "fragment", "Opt_4": "status", "Answer": "status", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "situation", "Opt_3_def": "part of something", "Opt_4_def": "position, standing"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Microsoft has promised that the forthcoming operating system will be more ____ than ever before.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "secure", "Opt_3": "reliable", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "secure", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "safe", "Opt_3_def": "by terrorists lies in the countries that possess such devices.", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Newspaper headline: MIT scientists devise a new way to ____ gene therapy.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "clarify", "Opt_3": "deliver", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "deliver", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_3_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "All the ESL student's teachers can ____ influence the speed at which he or she learns English.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Why did the Bush Administration refuse to ____ its goals in order to achieve a consensus?", "Opt_1": "employ", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "modify", "Opt_4": "conclude", "Answer": "modify", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to finish; to make a judgment"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Modern computers can ____ the equivalent of many millions of pages of writing.", "Opt_1": "undertake", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "impress", "Opt_4": "store", "Answer": "store", "Opt_1_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Victims of terrorist attacks are usually given ____ by the government.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "surplus", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "growth", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "development, increase"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government's plan to kill all infected cows in the ____ is sure to produce an angry response from the farmers.", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "principle", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "rule"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Typically held the 3rd week of February, this is an annual event that helps College of Fine Arts students explore careers, develop strategies to ____ career and artistic goals successfully.", "Opt_1": "produce", "Opt_2": "pursue", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "devote", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to make or create", "Opt_2_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to give (time) to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian region have in common ____ being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you are applying from a country in which English is not the official language, you are required to submit ____ of English language proficiency.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "evidence", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "proof, signs"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "To accommodate the great power ____ now rapidly occurring in Asia, the United States needs vigorous preparation by its executive branch and Congress.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "shift", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "shift", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "change", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The lesson plans contained an incomplete description of learners, their background and ____ knowledge.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "An orange pencil is not a ____ tool to do your homework with.", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "characteristic", "Opt_3": "straightforward", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "suitable", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "typical", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The results on the tests are ____ to expectations.", "Opt_1": "fallacy", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "penalty", "Answer": "contrary", "Opt_1_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "negative consequence; punishment"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is a ____ at our school to have a pizza party for the new students.", "Opt_1": "response", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "implication", "Answer": "custom", "Opt_1_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "result or consequence"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "An analysis of the historical causes of slavery is ____ the scope of this course.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The State Department has seen a ____ increase in passport applications being filed since a recent change in policy.", "Opt_1": "temporary", "Opt_2": "slight", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "drastic", "Answer": "drastic", "Opt_1_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_2_def": "small", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "severe; great"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Doctors ____ the difficulty of giving up smoking. That's why they recommend never starting.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "recognize", "Opt_3": "convince", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_3_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Storage of personal information not related to university business must be limited and must not ____ in any way with the storage and maintenance of university data.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "verify", "Opt_3": "permit", "Opt_4": "develop", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_3_def": "to allow", "Opt_4_def": "to grow or improve"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This position is the ____ chance to learn about the many different areas of marketing and business operations in a hands-on environment.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "abundant", "Opt_3": "sole", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "ultimate", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_3_def": "only", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Library and information science students must be taught how to exploit the resources that will allow them to ____ the future and avoid becoming irrelevant as information professionals.", "Opt_1": "organize", "Opt_2": "monitor", "Opt_3": "anticipate", "Opt_4": "suspect", "Answer": "anticipate", "Opt_1_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_2_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_3_def": "to expect", "Opt_4_def": "to believe"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "What might cause my computer to ____ oddly and even insult me, and how can I fix it?", "Opt_1": "commence", "Opt_2": "distort", "Opt_3": "behave", "Opt_4": "ban", "Answer": "behave", "Opt_1_def": "to start", "Opt_2_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_3_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to prohibit or forbid"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Giving up the course was a ____ thing to do. He had no chance of passing it.", "Opt_1": "concise", "Opt_2": "rational", "Opt_3": "subjective", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "rational", "Opt_1_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_2_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_3_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Future research would need to ensure that participants did not engage in any other activities immediately ____ to the study at hand.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The suggestion is ____ not reasonable, and the department need not adopt it.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Advertising marketed directly to the consumer may minimize the risks and ____ the benefits of medications.", "Opt_1": "append", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "invest", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to put money into something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A student who is in debt to the University at the end of any academic ____ shall not be permitted to register in the University again.", "Opt_1": "order", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "statement", "Opt_4": "term", "Answer": "term", "Opt_1_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_4_def": "a word or expression"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Each of these mechanisms has been investigated with a variety of blood sucking insects and the results clearly show that mosquitoes cannot ____ AidS.", "Opt_1": "transmit", "Opt_2": "assure", "Opt_3": "dominate", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "transmit", "Opt_1_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_3_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Does anyone really believe that governments will ____ tax incomes on trillions of dollars of e-commerce sales?", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "forego", "Opt_3": "respect", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "forego", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_3_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Testing personnel will not confront any tester who is cheating, but will complete the Testing Incident Report and ____ to the supervisor.", "Opt_1": "predict", "Opt_2": "cooperate", "Opt_3": "submit", "Opt_4": "qualify", "Answer": "submit", "Opt_1_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_2_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_3_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_4_def": "to become eligible"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In this particular poem, Dalton, while asking what woman's ____ is, also advises man on woman's potential and her proper place in life.", "Opt_1": "sphere", "Opt_2": "outline", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "sphere", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest", "Opt_2_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This emphasis on improving student outcomes will persist in the ____ future as the dominant factor in determining the success or failure of education reform strategies.", "Opt_1": "immediate", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "absent", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "immediate", "Opt_1_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He is the inevitable ____ for the leading role in the play. He's by far the best actor in the school.", "Opt_1": "choice", "Opt_2": "ratio", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "choice", "Opt_1_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Solving a problem of this ____ will require the collective will and shared sacrifice of all members of the university.", "Opt_1": "magnitude", "Opt_2": "legislation", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "course", "Answer": "magnitude", "Opt_1_def": "size; amount", "Opt_2_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "a subject or period of study"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The university has no ____ to refund the fee after the second week of the semester.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "hypothesis", "Opt_4": "event", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_4_def": "a happening"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Since it was founded in 1999, the partnership program has been a key element in the dramatic ____ in applications to the College.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "offer", "Opt_3": "violate", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In an article in the March 11, 2004 issue of Nature, the investigators report that female mice ____ the ability to make new egg cells well into adulthood.", "Opt_1": "seek", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "retain", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We cannot allow a few disaffected children to continually ____ the education of the majority of the class.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "formulate", "Opt_3": "amend", "Opt_4": "interrupt", "Answer": "interrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to express", "Opt_3_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_4_def": "to stop something from happening"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The manager has decided form a committee to ____ the recent increase in theft from the storeroom.", "Opt_1": "consent", "Opt_2": "adopt", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "transfer", "Answer": "investigate", "Opt_1_def": "to agree", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to move to a different place or job"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school is will continue to undergo problems in its attempt to ____ new students unless it reduces its tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "migrate", "Opt_3": "defend", "Opt_4": "edit", "Answer": "attract", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_3_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_4_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The police chief gave a very different version of the incident than the TV reporter the ____ day.", "Opt_1": "dynamic", "Opt_2": "previous", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "previous", "Opt_1_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_2_def": "the one before", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It was a very ____ test. Everyone got 100%.", "Opt_1": "previous", "Opt_2": "straightforward", "Opt_3": "classic", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "straightforward", "Opt_1_def": "the one before", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He has lost the desire to consider what is right and wrong because he was hurt, ____ devastated, when the love of his life disappeared.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The nine women here say the poor ____ of domestic workers is an apartheid-era relic that has no place in democratic South Africa.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "phase", "Opt_4": "term", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_4_def": "a word or expression"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is essential that governments take ____ before making the decision to go to war.", "Opt_1": "apparatus", "Opt_2": "feature", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Tourists who visit a foreign city often employ a ____ to show them the most interesting things to see.", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "guide", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "guide", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Increased income caused consumers to spend more and firms to ____ more.", "Opt_1": "include", "Opt_2": "invest", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "drain", "Answer": "invest", "Opt_1_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_2_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to take away; to get rid of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government's ____ in his second term of office is to reduce child poverty.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "priority", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The fighting is expected to ____ when the United Nations sends in its observers.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "accumulate", "Answer": "cease", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "to grow; to gather together"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The doctor began to ____ that her patient was not telling the whole truth about what was wrong.", "Opt_1": "force", "Opt_2": "realize", "Opt_3": "derive", "Opt_4": "correspond", "Answer": "realize", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_2_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_3_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_4_def": "to be related to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The United States is a nation pulling apart to a ____ unknown in the last 25 years.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "degree", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "degree", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A student whose total absences in a course, excused or unexcused, exceed ten per trimester is liable to ____ the course.", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "fail", "Opt_4": "determine", "Answer": "fail", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is possible to find the ____ of an object by measuring the amount of water that it displaces.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "volume", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "event", "Answer": "volume", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "a happening"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The company made a radical reduction in its workforce in order to improve its ____ in the second part of the financial year.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "equipment", "Opt_3": "task", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_3_def": "job", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Not all scientists agree that thought disorder and language disorder are ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "public", "Opt_2": "proper", "Opt_3": "optional", "Opt_4": "discrete", "Answer": "discrete", "Opt_1_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_2_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_3_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_4_def": "separate"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He is learning that treatments that worked fine in cities don't always fare well here, where patients may drive ____ hours to obtain medical care.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "various", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "several", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Doctors should give ____ advice and treatment to all patients, whether rich or poor.", "Opt_1": "eligible", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "uniform", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many of the faculty and students we talked with wanted to ____ anonymous and asked that they not be listed by name in our report.", "Opt_1": "remain", "Opt_2": "comprehend", "Opt_3": "suppress", "Opt_4": "broadcast", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_2_def": "to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This course traces the ____ concept of the hero by reading selected works by authors such as Homer, Plutarch and Caesar,", "Opt_1": "ancient", "Opt_2": "mental", "Opt_3": "steady", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "very old", "Opt_2_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_3_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Bush administration will not back down on pursuing new sanctions against Iran over its nuclear program ____ questions about their effectiveness.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The last ____ of the twentieth century started in 1990 and ended on 31 December 1999.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "decade", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "decade", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The tree responds this way because the tree needs to ____ food again before it starves.", "Opt_1": "manufacture", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "arise", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to happen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Archaeologists found some Roman coins ____ the town wall.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There was not a big difference in the negative description of Saddam Hussein among the three newspapers, and these descriptions did not ____ much space.", "Opt_1": "prevail", "Opt_2": "occupy", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "allocate", "Answer": "occupy", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_2_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to give to (to promise to give)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The writer clearly did not perform the experiment, but gave us what her very great ____ expected would happen.", "Opt_1": "ignorance", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "reply", "Opt_4": "contrast", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "an answer", "Opt_4_def": "difference"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She made it clear many times throughout the work that she did not believe in and did not want to ____ in the concept and institution of marriage.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "increase", "Opt_3": "derive", "Opt_4": "emerge", "Answer": "participate", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_3_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_4_def": "to come out; to become known"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The idea was to ____ the possibility of a local court or government treating a foreign investor unfairly.", "Opt_1": "reserve", "Opt_2": "remove", "Opt_3": "trigger", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to take away", "Opt_3_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We used this information to ____ a continuous measure of the ratio of subject-specific coursework to total coursework.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "exist", "Opt_3": "construct", "Opt_4": "persist", "Answer": "construct", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_3_def": "to make", "Opt_4_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Most companies guarantee to ____ machines, like refrigerators or computers, if they break down in the first year.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "undertake", "Opt_3": "replace", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "replace", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_3_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I'm not sure he understands the ____ of the project. He will need to spend at least two hours on it every day for the next 3 weeks.", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "scope", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "extent, range", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The applicant's qualifications must ____ to the qualifications required to perform the duties of the position as indicated in the job description.", "Opt_1": "present", "Opt_2": "correlate", "Opt_3": "raise", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "correlate", "Opt_1_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_2_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_3_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Tourists who visit a foreign city often ____ a guide to show them the most interesting things to see.", "Opt_1": "donate", "Opt_2": "recur", "Opt_3": "defend", "Opt_4": "employ", "Answer": "employ", "Opt_1_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_2_def": "to happen again", "Opt_3_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone; to use"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "For reasons that are not yet completely clear, practice and theory usually ____ at this point.", "Opt_1": "comprehend", "Opt_2": "avoid", "Opt_3": "decline", "Opt_4": "diverge", "Answer": "diverge", "Opt_1_def": "to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_3_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to move apart; to be different from"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school is constructing a new science block ____ the sports field.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "His written work is actually very good, but he has ____ problems with the difficult English spelling system.", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "sound", "Opt_4": "obvious", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "good; strong", "Opt_4_def": "clear, evident"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is possible this information was ignored because it was not ____ or because it was simply unavailable.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Her frequent absence from school is the ____ reason for her bad grades in the final exams.", "Opt_1": "apparent", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "instant", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "immediate"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Science should be about objective facts, not ____ opinions.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "genuine", "Opt_3": "regular", "Opt_4": "external", "Answer": "subjective", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_3_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_4_def": "outside"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Government ministers should not ____ on matters outside of their own domain; they often do not know enough about such topics.", "Opt_1": "comment", "Opt_2": "command", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "profession", "Answer": "comment", "Opt_1_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_2_def": "control", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "job; occupation"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I ____ his strange behaviour recently is the result of his parents' divorce.", "Opt_1": "suspend", "Opt_2": "assume", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "assume", "Opt_1_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_2_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Dr. Pruitt said that he was very ____ that all aspects of the law, as well as any other concerns, would be closely looked at prior to any deal being made.", "Opt_1": "formal", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "characteristic", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "confident", "Opt_1_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "typical", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "And, further, he didn't ____ a lecture from one whose own morality has been deficient.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "refute", "Opt_3": "appreciate", "Opt_4": "trigger", "Answer": "appreciate", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_3_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_4_def": "to (cause to) start"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The US Senate voted yesterday to provide \ufffd\ufffd4 billion for antiviral drugs and other measures to ____ for a feared influenza epidemic.", "Opt_1": "appeal", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "anticipate", "Answer": "prepare", "Opt_1_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to expect"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Lincoln, while receiving a majority vote ____ northerners, did not receive a majority of ALL the popular votes.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "When Penn State decided not to cancel classes, it seemed like a safe and ____ decision.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "deliberate", "Opt_4": "absent", "Answer": "sane", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_4_def": "being not there; missing"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It would not be wise to ____ from our planned course of action.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "withdraw", "Answer": "deviate", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to go back or take away"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "During various stages of a planning process, review and crosscheck the goals and objectives in the plan elements so that they do not ____ one another.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "frustrate", "Opt_3": "enter", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If your exam is closed book, you will want to prepare an outline that will ____ you in studying until the day of the exam.", "Opt_1": "persuade", "Opt_2": "assist", "Opt_3": "utilize", "Opt_4": "adhere", "Answer": "assist", "Opt_1_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_2_def": "to help", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to keep to; to follow"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Difficult financial times must not force us to ____ the integration of teaching and research.", "Opt_1": "abandon", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "label", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "abandon", "Opt_1_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "When you finish unit 1, please do the questions and then ____ to unit 3. You don't need to do unit 2.", "Opt_1": "proceed", "Opt_2": "offer", "Opt_3": "descend", "Opt_4": "damage", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_2_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_3_def": "to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Parents who are alcoholics often ____ their children both physically. and emotionally.", "Opt_1": "admit", "Opt_2": "neglect", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "migrate", "Answer": "neglect", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_2_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to go to another place"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is slightly down from the 19 percent failure ____ last year but still significantly above the failure ____ in other freshmen subjects.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "symbol", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "His problems are largely ____ to poor concentration in class.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some scientists believe that genetically modified food can ____ people's health.", "Opt_1": "procure", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "deny", "Opt_4": "address", "Answer": "harm", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_4_def": "to give attention to (an issue)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The purpose of the study is to examine the hypothesis that ____ life is more stressful than rural life.", "Opt_1": "concise", "Opt_2": "urban", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "supplementary", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_2_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "extra; additional"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The two teams are ____ equal. It's difficult to predict who is going to win.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "fairly", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Various approaches to environmental ____ are discussed, along with steps in the planning process when citizen involvement is particularly effective.", "Opt_1": "design", "Opt_2": "justice", "Opt_3": "device", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "justice", "Opt_1_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_2_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_3_def": "object; method", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The writer clearly did not perform the experiment, but gave us what her very great ____ expected would happen.", "Opt_1": "incentive", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "instruction", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some people are unwilling to address the ____ of global warming. They claim it is not happening.", "Opt_1": "asset", "Opt_2": "goal", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "treatment", "Answer": "issue", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Tests are valid when they measure what they claim to measure, and ____ when they measure consistently.", "Opt_1": "reliable", "Opt_2": "intrinsic", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "reliable", "Opt_1_def": "by terrorists lies in the countries that possess such devices.", "Opt_2_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Every ____ in this class has made excellent progress and passed the final exam.", "Opt_1": "credit", "Opt_2": "individual", "Opt_3": "section", "Opt_4": "assent", "Answer": "individual", "Opt_1_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_2_def": "one person", "Opt_3_def": "part", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The library is going to ____ a new electronic system for checking out books.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "seek", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "introduce", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you want to live a long and healthy life, it is essential that you eat well and take get ____ of exercise.", "Opt_1": "point", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The requirements threaten to decrease family and individual student control over the ____ process.", "Opt_1": "transition", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "justice", "Opt_4": "interpretation", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_4_def": "explanation; assessment"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He found a serious error in the work and did a very careful study to ____ the correct results.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "determine", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "negotiate", "Answer": "determine", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Doctors ____ the difficulty of giving up smoking. That's why they recommend never starting.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "control", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "recognize", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many shops these days have ____ doors. They open as soon as you approach.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "automatic", "Opt_4": "complex", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, complicated"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "On your first day in a new school it is difficult to ____ all the information that you are given.", "Opt_1": "produce", "Opt_2": "assimilate", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "prevail", "Answer": "assimilate", "Opt_1_def": "to make or create", "Opt_2_def": "to take in", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed; to overcome"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It was ____ luck that he got a good grade in the test. He hadn't studied for it at all.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "local", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "pure", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You need to ____ all your PE clothes so that they can easily be returned to you if you lose them.", "Opt_1": "abandon", "Opt_2": "employ", "Opt_3": "attach", "Opt_4": "label", "Answer": "label", "Opt_1_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_3_def": "to put together with", "Opt_4_def": "to give a name to someone or something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "An analysis of the historical causes of slavery is ____ the scope of this course.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "One ____ result of rainy weather is that the dust is regularly washed off, reducing problems with the machinery.", "Opt_1": "perpetual", "Opt_2": "optional", "Opt_3": "faint", "Opt_4": "fortunate", "Answer": "fortunate", "Opt_1_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_2_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_3_def": "not strong", "Opt_4_def": "lucky"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This statement does not ____ that the university will be responsible for any other expenses of the above-name student.", "Opt_1": "imply", "Opt_2": "submit", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "affect", "Answer": "imply", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to have an influence on"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "How many planet/planet collisions do you ____ will come from the M31 incident - or do you think we will be smoothly assimilated?", "Opt_1": "presume", "Opt_2": "release", "Opt_3": "appoint", "Opt_4": "diverge", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_2_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_4_def": "to move apart; to be different from"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is usually a close ____ between students of the same nationality at an international school.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "schedule", "Opt_3": "duration", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "timetable", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Our focus is to motivate each student to achieve their full potential as they ____ for success in our five cornerstones of Academic Excellence.", "Opt_1": "respect", "Opt_2": "strive", "Opt_3": "sustain", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "strive", "Opt_1_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_2_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_3_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Infinite power is so ____ and incomprehensible an idea that the mind of man must necessarily be bewildered in the contemplation of it.", "Opt_1": "vast", "Opt_2": "considerable", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "actual", "Answer": "vast", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "real"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "These two-word verbs present one other problem, ____ not appearing as separate entries in the dictionary.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most people were ____ the plan to boycott the Olympics. Nevertheless, the government decided to do so.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Mobile phones have made it ____ to contact someone anytime and anywhere.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "loose", "Opt_3": "invisible", "Opt_4": "typical", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_4_def": "usual"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Aschoff's trip failed because he was unable to ____ his concept against the competitive approach favored by German and Russian scientists.", "Opt_1": "defend", "Opt_2": "advise", "Opt_3": "assure", "Opt_4": "anticipate", "Answer": "defend", "Opt_1_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_2_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_4_def": "to expect"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Biological processes ____ strongly with physical and chemical processes to create the planetary environment.", "Opt_1": "diminish", "Opt_2": "interact", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "emerge", "Answer": "interact", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_2_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to come out; to become known"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "When a block of wood is gently put into still water, it will descend by the ____ of gravity, until it has displaced a quantity of water, equal to its own.", "Opt_1": "combine", "Opt_2": "entitle", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "force", "Opt_1_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_2_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Your ____ heart rate is a useful way of pacing yourself during exercise.", "Opt_1": "dispute", "Opt_2": "target", "Opt_3": "symptom", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "target", "Opt_1_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_2_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_3_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The B grade had come to signify work that was ____ acceptable.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was found, in a bad ____ of repair and covered with moss and rust.", "Opt_1": "state", "Opt_2": "constraint", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This year you cannot choose which science course to do, but when you are in grade 9 you can ____ chemistry, physics or biology.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "announce", "Opt_3": "compel", "Opt_4": "select", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_3_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_4_def": "to choose"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He has a ____ chance of getting in to Oxford University if he gets top scores in all his exams.", "Opt_1": "utter", "Opt_2": "slight", "Opt_3": "spare", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "slight", "Opt_1_def": "complete, total", "Opt_2_def": "small", "Opt_3_def": "not needed", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you don't start working harder, we will ____ your right to leave the school at lunchtime.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "reward", "Opt_3": "restore", "Opt_4": "withdraw", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_4_def": "to go back or take away"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The men searched the ____ camp, digging beneath the snow and even into the earth, but no paper was found, no diaries and no documents.", "Opt_1": "economic", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "widespread", "Opt_4": "entire", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "common", "Opt_4_def": "whole, all"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government's ____ to the demonstrations was to promise a public inquiry into the reasons for going to war.", "Opt_1": "scale", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "finance", "Answer": "response", "Opt_1_def": "extent", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to do with money and payment"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Your grades will continue to ____ unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "sustain", "Opt_2": "spread", "Opt_3": "transmit", "Opt_4": "deteriorate", "Answer": "deteriorate", "Opt_1_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_2_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_3_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I think Kerry's biggest error, as a politician, is that he failed to ____ himself from Bush in any meaningful way.", "Opt_1": "differentiate", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "express", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to say or mean"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Over the course of the period there is a steady rise in the ____ of the painter, sculptor, and architect and a growing sympathy expressed for the visual arts.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "status", "Opt_4": "aid", "Answer": "status", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "position, standing", "Opt_4_def": "help (often financial help)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In future we will increasingly need to ____ wind and sun power as fossil fuels such as coal and oil become more expensive.", "Opt_1": "enforce", "Opt_2": "inhibit", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "utilize", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "For example, in many manufacturing processes several nominally ____ bodies undergo multiple, concurrent, dynamic frictional contacts.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "firm", "Opt_4": "available", "Answer": "rigid", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_4_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "TOEFL is not the most ____ part of the application, but it is an unavoidable part, which sometimes can be quite painful and time- consuming.", "Opt_1": "crucial", "Opt_2": "sane", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "extremely important", "Opt_2_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Cor-----nd: The dashes ____ to the number of letters missing from the word.", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "deliver", "Opt_3": "correspond", "Opt_4": "unite", "Answer": "correspond", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_3_def": "to be related to", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Let me ____ again that you must work alone; you are not permitted to get help from anyone else.", "Opt_1": "decline", "Opt_2": "obey", "Opt_3": "reduce", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_3_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We have a painting at home that's very valuable. It must be ____ more than a million dollars!", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "As maintenance requirements and costs increase, fewer aircraft will be in a ____ state of readiness or mission-capable.", "Opt_1": "satisfactory", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "basic", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "satisfactory", "Opt_1_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "first or easy", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The catheter then deploys a small balloon at the ____ of the blood clot.", "Opt_1": "decade", "Opt_2": "site", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "notion", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_2_def": "place", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "idea; concept"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "All campus party noise must ____ by 12:00 Midnight.", "Opt_1": "arise", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "dispose", "Opt_4": "eliminate", "Answer": "cease", "Opt_1_def": "to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to dispose of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is important to note that the ____ at which refracted light travels is dependent upon the density of the materials it is traveling through.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "speed", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is our belief that the students were not given a fair hearing, and ____ that the punishment was unjust.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "furthermore", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Thousands of farm families are being forced off the land, and we are being told that it is an ____ consequence of technological progress.", "Opt_1": "inevitable", "Opt_2": "drastic", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "typical", "Answer": "inevitable", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "severe; great", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "usual"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Dairy farmers have led the latest in a long series of protests by agricultural associations, despite the ____ high prices for farm products.", "Opt_1": "stereotype", "Opt_2": "margin", "Opt_3": "portion", "Opt_4": "record", "Answer": "record", "Opt_1_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_2_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_3_def": "part, amount", "Opt_4_def": "evidence; documentation"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The new rules will ____ to anyone who has come to Germany in the last 10 years.", "Opt_1": "reform", "Opt_2": "apply", "Opt_3": "refuse", "Opt_4": "employ", "Answer": "apply", "Opt_1_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_2_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone; to use"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is, once again, not an argument ____ bilingual education, because studies have shown that children in well- designed bilingual programs do well.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Photoshop provides you with techniques used to ____ the quality of graphics and photographs.", "Opt_1": "adjust", "Opt_2": "explain", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "predict", "Answer": "adjust", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_2_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to say what will happen in the future"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Truman managed to win a narrow ____ with 49.5 percent of the popular vote.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "occasion", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "victory", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is ____ important that you don't miss the deadline.", "Opt_1": "extremely", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "accordingly", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "very", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is an opportunity to ____ a more demanding curriculum while having an equal opportunity to share in the full benefits of university life.", "Opt_1": "compete", "Opt_2": "pursue", "Opt_3": "derive", "Opt_4": "observe", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_3_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_4_def": "to watch carefully"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Attendance will not constitute a specific percentage of your final grade, but if you miss more than two classes you will ____ fail this course.", "Opt_1": "definitely", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "indeed", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A student who is in debt to the University at the end of any academic ____ shall not be permitted to register in the University again.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "scope", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "term", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "extent, range", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "To prevent this from happening, it is very helpful for patients to ____ talking unless absolutely necessary for three days following surgery.", "Opt_1": "distinguish", "Opt_2": "avoid", "Opt_3": "clarify", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_3_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He has made ____ progress all year and should have no trouble passing his exams.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "vast", "Answer": "smooth", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is not the government's role to ____ what people are doing when they are online.", "Opt_1": "promote", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "deserve", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "supervise", "Opt_1_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is only one error in your writing. You put: He play tennis ____ of He plays tennis.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is fair to ____ the government for their successful efforts to reduce unemployment among older people.", "Opt_1": "specify", "Opt_2": "store", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "praise", "Answer": "praise", "Opt_1_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_2_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "to express approval about something someone has done"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I suppose one thing I cannot do is ____ the film as I wished it had been made.", "Opt_1": "approach", "Opt_2": "restore", "Opt_3": "review", "Opt_4": "complicate", "Answer": "review", "Opt_1_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_2_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_3_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_4_def": "to make things more complex or difficult"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She ____ has to start attending school regularly. That will solve all her problems.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "merely", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We all have to tolerate differences of ____ in the political world and, in order to do that, we have to understand that there are real reasons for these differences.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "propensity", "Opt_3": "staff", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_3_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school is working on a ____ to give all students a portable computer for use in lessons.", "Opt_1": "stage", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "license", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "scheme", "Opt_1_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Your ____ task for this lesson is to work together to prepare a presentation on air pollution.", "Opt_1": "economic", "Opt_2": "related", "Opt_3": "extraordinary", "Opt_4": "main", "Answer": "main", "Opt_1_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_2_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_3_def": "very unusual", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ ended with a rebellion against the East India Company in 1857, and the firm eventually was nationalized.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "technique", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The most significant risk factor in predicting whether a person will commit a violent crime in the future is whether the person has ____ offenses.", "Opt_1": "previous", "Opt_2": "loose", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "previous", "Opt_1_def": "the one before", "Opt_2_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "short"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "When the Powhatans did not want to trade with the settlers, Smith used force to ____ food.", "Opt_1": "acquire", "Opt_2": "behave", "Opt_3": "recommend", "Opt_4": "trigger", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_4_def": "to (cause to) start"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Food prices are ____ rising again after many months of no change.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Scientists don't know how to ____ drought a month or more in advance for most locations.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "predict", "Opt_3": "join", "Opt_4": "invest", "Answer": "predict", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_3_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_4_def": "to put money into something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has no right to ____ how much people should or should not drink.", "Opt_1": "analyze", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "stress", "Opt_4": "raise", "Answer": "dictate", "Opt_1_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_4_def": "to lift; to make higher"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In response to these events, this study was initiated to define and investigate the ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "period", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The different religious groups ____ came to realize that none of them could hope to prevail over all the others.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "moreover", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If your exam is closed book, you will want to prepare an ____ that will assist you in studying until the day of the exam.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "opportunity", "Opt_3": "outline", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "outline", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "chance", "Opt_3_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Due to her student teaching commitments Murray was unable to ____ this year's event.", "Opt_1": "invest", "Opt_2": "conserve", "Opt_3": "refer", "Opt_4": "organize", "Answer": "organize", "Opt_1_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_2_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_3_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_4_def": "to put into (its proper) place"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "On the whole the great bulk of Canadian immigration of the past ____ has been drawn from the English-speaking countries.", "Opt_1": "generation", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "purpose", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "generation", "Opt_1_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You need to trust your ____ as to whether he is the right man to marry.", "Opt_1": "fee", "Opt_2": "supply", "Opt_3": "propensity", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_2_def": "provision, store", "Opt_3_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Institute must take greater measures to ____ students that they need not fear consequences when seeking medical help for substance abuse.", "Opt_1": "exclude", "Opt_2": "provoke", "Opt_3": "assure", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_2_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is hardly a surprise that national governments have failed to solve global problems, since they have also failed to solve their ____ domestic problems.", "Opt_1": "own", "Opt_2": "dispose", "Opt_3": "conceal", "Opt_4": "retreat", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_2_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to hide", "Opt_4_def": "to go back"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The basic ____ is, and always has been, one of parenting.", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "purpose", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "issue", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "School need to ____ their curricula on the needs of the students who attend them.", "Opt_1": "base", "Opt_2": "clarify", "Opt_3": "organize", "Opt_4": "cover", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_2_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_3_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to complete"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ of young men who walk around with large aggressive dogs is that they are from the working class and are criminals.", "Opt_1": "summary", "Opt_2": "progress", "Opt_3": "command", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_2_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_3_def": "control", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Groups should ____ the instructor if a member is unexpectedly absent and try to save materials for that person.", "Opt_1": "engage", "Opt_2": "anticipate", "Opt_3": "advise", "Opt_4": "withdraw", "Answer": "advise", "Opt_1_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_2_def": "to expect", "Opt_3_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_4_def": "to go back or take away"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is not difficult to ____ on what could happen to these laws if the computer really does change our attitude to knowledge.", "Opt_1": "coordinate", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "speculate", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It offers an effective solution to a problem based on good audience analysis, and fulfills ____ as well as all major purposes.", "Opt_1": "willing", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "relevant", "Opt_4": "minor", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_4_def": "small, not important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As maintenance requirements and costs increase, fewer aircraft will be in a ____ state of readiness or mission-capable.", "Opt_1": "satisfactory", "Opt_2": "perpetual", "Opt_3": "prime", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "satisfactory", "Opt_1_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_2_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The (German) invention of the dynamo brought a revolution in electrical energy leading to the construction of ____ stations serving cities and towns.", "Opt_1": "transition", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "power", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "the right or authority to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Telephone and telegraph ____ from the Greek words meaning far speak and far write.", "Opt_1": "fade", "Opt_2": "incorporate", "Opt_3": "derive", "Opt_4": "multiply", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_2_def": "to include", "Opt_3_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_4_def": "to increase greatly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you ____ your calculator like that, you'll break it.", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "restore", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "abuse", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There are ____ areas under the sea that have not yet been explored.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "vast", "Opt_4": "concise", "Answer": "vast", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "short, not detailed"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Richards understood the importance of her position, the ____ that she projected and the need to preserve her papers and records at the Center.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "task", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "job"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Sufficient progress has been made with regard to drinking water to place within reach the target of halving the proportion of the population without ____ to safe drinking water between 1990 and 2015.", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "citizen", "Opt_3": "access", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_3_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She lied to the ____ and cheated in her test, but because of her family situation, it was decided to allow her to stay.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "principal", "Opt_3": "dynamic", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_4_def": "large"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The temperature curve shows that the increase was not steady with time; a fact which could ____ be expected and is also not observed on other continents.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "merely", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you wish to remain at this school, you will have to ____ to its rules.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "discuss", "Opt_3": "convey", "Opt_4": "conform", "Answer": "conform", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about", "Opt_3_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_4_def": "to do what is required"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you choose to do nothing to ____ to the changing conditions, you will probably make yourself miserable.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "adapt", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This year you cannot choose which science course to do, but when you are in grade 9 you can ____ chemistry, physics or biology.", "Opt_1": "trust", "Opt_2": "select", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "found", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_2_def": "to choose", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to begin (often an organization)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government has set the ____ target of halving child poverty by the year 2020.", "Opt_1": "scarce", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "faint", "Opt_4": "ambitious", "Answer": "ambitious", "Opt_1_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "not strong", "Opt_4_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Perhaps the most ____ example of an arthropod joint, indeed one of the most complex skeletal structures known, is the wing hinge of insects.", "Opt_1": "elaborate", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "evident", "Answer": "elaborate", "Opt_1_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "clear"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I do not wish to ____ that she is lazy, but her work is often late and of poor quality.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "imply", "Opt_3": "signify", "Opt_4": "descend", "Answer": "imply", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to go down"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This course traces the ancient ____ of the hero by reading selected works by authors such as Homer, Plutarch and Caesar,", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "concept", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There's no ____ to make an effort if the teacher never gives you back your work.", "Opt_1": "exhibit", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "scope", "Opt_4": "incentive", "Answer": "incentive", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "extent, range", "Opt_4_def": "reason to do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We must find a way to ____ the new questioning skills along with the new curriculum when the funding is gone.", "Opt_1": "create", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "sustain", "Answer": "sustain", "Opt_1_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to keep going; to maintain"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "More than 70 percent of the surveyed firms said that the lack of housing was not a ____ on their ability to expand.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "conflict", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "item", "Answer": "constraint", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "thing, element"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Each student's experience was so varied that I was unable to ____ common themes for discussion.", "Opt_1": "isolate", "Opt_2": "discuss", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "These questions are meant to help you research the background information you will need to ____ some of the water quality issues in NYC.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "extend", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We have a painting at home that's very valuable. It must be ____ more than a million dollars!", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Those who had seen the march in Weimar at the 1926 party rally knew that National Socialism's march to ____ could not be halted.", "Opt_1": "motive", "Opt_2": "contract", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "victory", "Answer": "victory", "Opt_1_def": "reason", "Opt_2_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "win"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Beethoven was not an ideal parent and enormous ____ developed between the two, contributing to his son's attempted suicide in 1826.", "Opt_1": "concept", "Opt_2": "disaster", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "friction", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_2_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "All the ESL student's teachers can ____ influence the speed at which he or she learns English.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "too"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is a ____ to think that you can put off working until the week before the exam and still pass it.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "pressure", "Opt_4": "issue", "Answer": "fallacy", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_4_def": "a matter or problem"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Her family were persecuted by the Nazis, so it's no surprise that she shows ____ against the Germans.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "method", "Opt_4": "bias", "Answer": "bias", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Kennan had no ____ that the Soviets had regional, if not global, ambitions.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "facilities", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "doubt", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Wurtz said that these products are not just ____ unnecessary, they are even potentially dangerous.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is ____ important to remember that parents as a group have not usually taken the riding lessons and are not competent to supervise their children.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In a densely populated area, an earthquake may do far more damage than one of greater ____ that occurs in a remote area.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "magnitude", "Opt_3": "propensity", "Opt_4": "description", "Answer": "magnitude", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "size; amount", "Opt_3_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_4_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Chelsea and Liverpool are ____ the 2nd and 3rd most successful football clubs.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "respectively", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Advertising marketed directly to the consumer may minimize the risks and ____ the benefits of medications.", "Opt_1": "tend", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "extend", "Opt_4": "exaggerate", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_4_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is a ____ chance to visit South Africa, and at the same time help build a school in the desert.", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "broad", "Opt_3": "valid", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "unique", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_3_def": "correct", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Germany is no longer a ____ society. Between 15 - 20% of its population is non-German.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "faint", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "not strong", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In an effective group, each person can ____ sufficient influence on the decisions of the group to prevent the group from setting unattainable goals.", "Opt_1": "trust", "Opt_2": "exert", "Opt_3": "constitute", "Opt_4": "analyze", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_4_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You are ____ of much better grades if you make more effort.", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "capable", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "capable", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "able", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Click here to review the rules of comma usage when you combine two ____ clauses.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "firm", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many German companies have decided to ____ their factories to parts of the world where workers are cheaper.", "Opt_1": "reform", "Opt_2": "encourage", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "transfer", "Opt_1_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_2_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The minister gave an ____ answer when asked if the government intended to raise taxes.", "Opt_1": "formal", "Opt_2": "urgent", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_2_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Due to its association with the churches and schools, the Samoan language enjoyed high ____ in Tokelau for a long time.", "Opt_1": "prestige", "Opt_2": "topic", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "commodity", "Answer": "prestige", "Opt_1_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "a product; something you can buy"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It only drew more ____ to the 13-year-old Robertson panel report and the CIA's role in the investigation of UFOs.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "attention", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "focus", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Omitting the transportation costs would ____ the company's financial position.", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "revise", "Opt_3": "conduct", "Opt_4": "distort", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_3_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_4_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some parents or guardians who place their children temporarily in foster care do so because they cannot ____ their abilities to raise their children.", "Opt_1": "indicate", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "dictate", "Opt_4": "praise", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_4_def": "to express approval about something someone has done"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Facts surrounding the diagnosis of the child's ____ are in serious dispute.", "Opt_1": "transition", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "scope", "Opt_4": "condition", "Answer": "condition", "Opt_1_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "extent, range", "Opt_4_def": "state"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There were many ____ but complex reasons why he gave up his well-paid job.", "Opt_1": "visual", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "sane", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "sane", "Opt_1_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Though Sima and Codreanu both attempted to prevent the murder, it ____ took place, and produced harsh consequences.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "To prevent this from happening, it is very helpful for patients to avoid talking unless ____ necessary for three days following surgery.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I will ____ my presentation with an example of sea pollution.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "ensure", "Opt_3": "appoint", "Opt_4": "publish", "Answer": "conclude", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_4_def": "to make available in paper or online form"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is ____ unusual considering the 1997 survey's response of 41%.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Counselors will begin on-going sessions with a student only after having obtained signed ____ of the student and signed consent of the parent.", "Opt_1": "assent", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "assent", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Our results did not ____ us to determine whether SMR or MOEE had reached minimum values.", "Opt_1": "enable", "Opt_2": "oppose", "Opt_3": "trust", "Opt_4": "attain", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_3_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_4_def": "to get, achieve"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This unnecessary ____ would adversely impact the existing review system that ensures the high quality of scientific research in the United States.", "Opt_1": "minimum", "Opt_2": "vary", "Opt_3": "legislation", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "legislation", "Opt_1_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_2_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_3_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ is planning to extend the school day until 4pm.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "aspect", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "friction", "Answer": "administration", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government will never ____ drug-taking, but it should do more to reduce the number of school-age drug users.", "Opt_1": "eliminate", "Opt_2": "destroy", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "eliminate", "Opt_1_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_2_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "But it is not a ____ for comprehensive food safety programs throughout the food distribution system.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "survey", "Opt_3": "substitute", "Opt_4": "concept", "Answer": "substitute", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_3_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_4_def": "idea; understanding"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Please note that section 5 is the most important, and ____ it should constitute the majority of your journal entry.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "hence", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government's plan to kill all infected cows in the ____ is sure to produce an angry response from the farmers.", "Opt_1": "exhibit", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "fault", "Opt_4": "factor", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_4_def": "an aspect to be considered"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most people are shocked by the ____ of life in Iraq since the invasion a few years ago.", "Opt_1": "surplus", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "level", "Opt_4": "loss", "Answer": "loss", "Opt_1_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_4_def": "removal or reduction"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Most leadership training programs leave out the key question, ____ how leaders actually affect their groups.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "respectively", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The siting and design are a typical ____ of ancient buildings that belong to a self-enclosed precinct.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "previous", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "characteristic", "Answer": "characteristic", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "the one before", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "typical"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The suggestion is ____ not reasonable, and the department need not adopt it.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "recently", "Opt_3": "accordingly", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "in the near past", "Opt_3_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The father stated he was from the neighbourhood of Bandon, where he had been unable to ____ any employment.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "procure", "Opt_3": "adhere", "Opt_4": "belong", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_4_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Clinton certainly did not ____ these word games, but in recent years they have risen to a high art form in Washington.", "Opt_1": "invent", "Opt_2": "comprise", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "invent", "Opt_1_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_2_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The paper was unable to ____ sufficient support and ceased publication after a few months.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "attract", "Opt_3": "devote", "Opt_4": "invest", "Answer": "attract", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_3_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_4_def": "to put money into something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Audio software can help students to record their spoken words describing an abstract ____ or how to perform a computation.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "trace", "Answer": "concept", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "sign; indication; evidence"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "But, for their part, the Syrian leaders failed to ____ for Israel to have rights to some of that water.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "evaluate", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "negotiate", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ for her frequent absences will be a poor grade in the final exam.", "Opt_1": "district", "Opt_2": "exponent", "Opt_3": "penalty", "Opt_4": "bias", "Answer": "penalty", "Opt_1_def": "region of a city", "Opt_2_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_4_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I am no expert in animal behavior, but anyone with even a ____ knowledge of the field must be impressed with their complex forms of social behavior.", "Opt_1": "original", "Opt_2": "elementary", "Opt_3": "optional", "Opt_4": "slight", "Answer": "slight", "Opt_1_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_4_def": "small"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Being overweight is no longer simply a health problem - it is a ____ of a greater cultural shift that shows no sign of fading.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "symptom", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "symptom", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school plans to ____ the sports field so that games can be played after dark.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "illuminate", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Therefore he was unable to ____ that he was breaking new methodological ground.", "Opt_1": "maintain", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "focus", "Answer": "maintain", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some people think it was no ____ that there was a terror alarm two days before the election.", "Opt_1": "device", "Opt_2": "result", "Opt_3": "gap", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "object; method", "Opt_2_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_3_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This process is more ____ in those sciences in which the technological requirements have increased to a significant extent.", "Opt_1": "evident", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "vast", "Answer": "evident", "Opt_1_def": "clear", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The head teacher could not ____ parents that there would be no increase in school fees.", "Opt_1": "degenerate", "Opt_2": "examine", "Opt_3": "assure", "Opt_4": "correlate", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_4_def": "to have a close connection"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The most significant ____ factor in predicting whether a person will commit a violent crime in the future is whether the person has previous offenses.", "Opt_1": "promote", "Opt_2": "measure", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "praise", "Answer": "risk", "Opt_1_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_2_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to express approval about something someone has done"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The management wanted to ____ the incompetent employee but could find no-one better to replace him.", "Opt_1": "disturb", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "dismiss", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "dismiss", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students who take the class are expected to choose a contemporary problem they would like to address and ____ with each other in researching it.", "Opt_1": "collaborate", "Opt_2": "acknowledge", "Opt_3": "solve", "Opt_4": "undergo", "Answer": "collaborate", "Opt_1_def": "to work together", "Opt_2_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_3_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_4_def": "to receive or experience"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ of weight change through pregnancy was similar across the 3 projects.", "Opt_1": "exhibit", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "challenge", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "pattern", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You have made no effort to learn, ____ you will not be entered for the test.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The OCC provides ____ and legal advice in the development of policy, procedures, and strategy related to the management and operation of the UC Riverside campus.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "order", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You should ____ a little more in class discussions. This will help to improve your spoken English.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "consume", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "participate", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The OCC provides ____ and legal advice in the development of policy, procedures, and strategy related to the management and operation of the UC Riverside campus.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "alternative", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "scheme", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "other possibility", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "plan. idea, project"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Her consistent efforts throughout the school year are certain to ____ excellent results in her final examinations.", "Opt_1": "dominate", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "accompany", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Attendance will not constitute a specific percentage of your final grade, but if you miss more than two classes you will ____ fail this course.", "Opt_1": "definitely", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "especially", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "particularly", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Facts surrounding the ____ of the child's condition are in serious dispute.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "diagnosis", "Opt_3": "field", "Opt_4": "phenomenon", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_4_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government decided to ____ its economic policy after three years of very slow growth.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "prepare", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "dominate", "Answer": "alter", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The fact that he can only speak a little English is sure to ____ his already severe learning problems.", "Opt_1": "magnify", "Opt_2": "compel", "Opt_3": "impress", "Opt_4": "promote", "Answer": "magnify", "Opt_1_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_2_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_3_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It was in 1827, near the beginning of his time ____ from the Allan family, that Poe witnessed his first collection of poetry.", "Opt_1": "similar", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "legitimate", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "correct; allowed"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "These interviews are part of an ____ effort to discover our internal best practices and high points.", "Opt_1": "intense", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "firm", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "intense", "Opt_1_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This is not the correct ____ to use when comparing two separate databases.", "Opt_1": "notion", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "procedure", "Answer": "procedure", "Opt_1_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "the way to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Job applicants often find that their personal attributes match what a company values; when this occurs, you should ____ these attributes in your CV.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "highlight", "Opt_4": "revive", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring back (to life)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is not always possible to distinguish a ____ of a conflict from a consequence of that conflict.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "cause", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "cause", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Students who get in the athletic teams enjoy a high ____ in the school community.", "Opt_1": "prestige", "Opt_2": "fragment", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "trace", "Answer": "prestige", "Opt_1_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_2_def": "part of something", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "sign; indication; evidence"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some people are unwilling to address the ____ of global warming. They claim it is not happening.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "debt", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "decade", "Answer": "issue", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "a period of ten years"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She didn't study for the vocabulary test, so ____ she got a low score.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "These results suggest that being treated as a sex ____ can undermine women's performance in stereotypically masculine domains.", "Opt_1": "affair", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "status", "Opt_4": "object", "Answer": "object", "Opt_1_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "position, standing", "Opt_4_def": "thing"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government received information but did not consider it ____ and therefore decided to ignore it.", "Opt_1": "reliable", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "precise", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "reliable", "Opt_1_def": "by terrorists lies in the countries that possess such devices.", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "exact", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The work involves some lifting and bending, and ____ requires travel away from the normal duty station.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Her family were persecuted by the Nazis, so it's no surprise that she shows bias ____ the Germans.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Digital television is not yet ____ in many parts of the country.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "external", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "outside"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She did not follow the directions on the label, ____ carefully reading it.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You will ____ a lengthy, very technical email, which in short, states that your unsubscribe request did not succeed.", "Opt_1": "connect", "Opt_2": "reverse", "Opt_3": "receive", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "All students whose college/university will be forwarding tuition payments will need to contact the OSA to find out the ____ procedure.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "average", "Opt_3": "exact", "Opt_4": "fundamental", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_3_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Advertising marketed directly to the consumer may minimize the risks and ____ the benefits of medications.", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "strive", "Opt_3": "evolve", "Opt_4": "cooperate", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_3_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_4_def": "to work (well) with another person"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The purpose of the study is to examine the hypothesis that ____ life is more stressful than rural life.", "Opt_1": "urban", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "artificial", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "not real or natural"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Scientists ____ to unwrap the sweet mystery of the sugar coat on bacteria.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "reward", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "seek", "Answer": "seek", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to look for or want"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There are very few people living today who were born ____ to the first world war.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The best remedy is to change the nutrient solution every week ____ of every two weeks.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "before"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The result of such abuse was increased poverty in Russia and lost ____ in the fairness of governmental institutions.", "Opt_1": "belief", "Opt_2": "attention", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "belief", "Opt_1_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_2_def": "focus", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Do we have an ____ to help the poor?", "Opt_1": "situation", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "behalf", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The New Investigator Competition is an award for the best paper by a graduate student, carrying with it a prize valued at ____ \ufffd\ufffd500.", "Opt_1": "hence", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "moreover", "Opt_4": "indeed", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_4_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Upon completion of your program requirements, you will need to apply for a license to teach in the ____ of Ohio.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "margin", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He rightly concludes that the end of the Cold War failed to ____ significant changes in the Horn of Africa or to improve the mutual security of states.", "Opt_1": "prefer", "Opt_2": "permit", "Opt_3": "induce", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to like better", "Opt_2_def": "to allow", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Doctors were unable to ____ the man who was pulled out of the icy river.", "Opt_1": "react", "Opt_2": "refuse", "Opt_3": "revive", "Opt_4": "dictate", "Answer": "revive", "Opt_1_def": "to respond", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_3_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_4_def": "to tell someone what to do"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has announced its ____ for the introduction of the new tax system over the next 5 years.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "schedule", "Opt_3": "function", "Opt_4": "magnitude", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "timetable", "Opt_3_def": "job or role", "Opt_4_def": "size; amount"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has increased ____ spending by 50% in the last two years.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "physical", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "of the body", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The different religious groups gradually came to realize that none of them could hope to ____ over all the others.", "Opt_1": "confirm", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "proceed", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "prevail", "Opt_1_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Therefore he was unable to ____ that he was breaking new methodological ground.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "retreat", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "maintain", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to go back", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "APA offers specific recommendations for eliminating ____ in language concerning race, disability, and sexuality.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "tradition", "Opt_3": "bias", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "bias", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_3_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Frankfurt International School has invited the local ____ to its Open Day.", "Opt_1": "evidence", "Opt_2": "gain", "Opt_3": "purpose", "Opt_4": "community", "Answer": "community", "Opt_1_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_2_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_3_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Unfortunately, heroines of this sort are not ____ in oral tales, and do not exist at all in any of the Grimm tales.", "Opt_1": "numerous", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "effective", "Opt_4": "unique", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "very many", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "good, working well", "Opt_4_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You can lessen your ____ of getting a cold in the winter if you avoid others who already have one!", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "magnify", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "shrink", "Answer": "risk", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The assessment was not independent of influence by Coca-Cola (i.e. the final report appeared to have been edited by Coca-Cola ____ to its release.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The main function of the committee is to ____ a plan for future development.", "Opt_1": "seek", "Opt_2": "recommend", "Opt_3": "exert", "Opt_4": "mention", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to say; state"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ of global warming is one of the more contentious ____s in science.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "issue", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "fund", "Answer": "issue", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "money collected for a particular purpose"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "However, continuous and systematic research on the ____ did not emerge until after World War II.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "disaster", "Opt_3": "section", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "disaster", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_3_def": "part", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The system uses a ____ inference engine that does not require users to explicitly provide information about the start or ending points of their journeys.", "Opt_1": "effective", "Opt_2": "superficial", "Opt_3": "classic", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "novel", "Opt_1_def": "good, working well", "Opt_2_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_3_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_4_def": "new"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A student enrolled in these types of courses really didn't get to know the instructor well and ____ did not feel any sense of community.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The department may admit students of superior promise but ____ preparation, provided that such students correct their deficiencies.", "Opt_1": "severe", "Opt_2": "deficient", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "willing", "Answer": "deficient", "Opt_1_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_2_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "happy or prepared to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "To prevent this from happening, it is very helpful for patients to avoid talking unless ____ necessary for three days following surgery.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "indirectly", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We are going to ____ this photograph to poster size and put it on the classroom wall.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "enlarge", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to make larger", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Students who are awarded an International Student Scholarship must fulfill the following requirements each semester in ____ to continue receiving this award.", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "All ____ parties have websites these days to inform people of their policies.", "Opt_1": "obsolete", "Opt_2": "political", "Opt_3": "equivalent", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "political", "Opt_1_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_2_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_3_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is a ____ belief among the public that the government lied about the reason for going to war.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "previous", "Opt_3": "diverse", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "the one before", "Opt_3_def": "many and different", "Opt_4_def": "common"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "What might cause my computer to ____ oddly and even insult me, and how can I fix it?", "Opt_1": "behave", "Opt_2": "predict", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "consult", "Answer": "behave", "Opt_1_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "On-line learning applications will continue to ____ as educational institutions and. business corporations seek new ways to expand their services.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "participate", "Opt_3": "multiply", "Opt_4": "force", "Answer": "multiply", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to take part", "Opt_3_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The winner of the competition must devise a plan to ____ greenhouse gases from the atmosphere without creating adverse effects.", "Opt_1": "remove", "Opt_2": "share", "Opt_3": "maintain", "Opt_4": "deviate", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to take away", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to be different"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is interesting to think about how teaching will ____ under the influence of digital technologies.", "Opt_1": "accomplish", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "contact", "Opt_4": "evolve", "Answer": "evolve", "Opt_1_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_4_def": "to develop (into something better)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The two parties paid for these mistakes through extremely poor ____ in the final national elections.", "Opt_1": "device", "Opt_2": "schedule", "Opt_3": "performance", "Opt_4": "objective", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "object; method", "Opt_2_def": "timetable", "Opt_3_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_4_def": "aim or goal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some scientists ____ that we cannot infer global warming on the basis of a just few years of hot weather.", "Opt_1": "claim", "Opt_2": "introduce", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "appeal", "Answer": "claim", "Opt_1_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You will have to ____ your documents to fit the required length.", "Opt_1": "encounter", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "edit", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you decide to apply, you will need to compile a full application including: ____ sheet, goals and plan letter, and project statement.", "Opt_1": "distort", "Opt_2": "trade", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "cover", "Opt_1_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Developments in computer technology may ____ make accurate weather forecasting possible.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "extremely", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "very"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school had similar exam results to last year, with the ____ion ____ that mathematics scores were a little higher.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There were complications with the pregnancy, so she had to ____ starting school for a semester.", "Opt_1": "diverge", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "decline", "Opt_4": "compel", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to force or make happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The most important ____ of the new design is that it consumes less power.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "expert", "Opt_3": "outline", "Opt_4": "feature", "Answer": "feature", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_3_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_4_def": "part, aspect"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Government agencies and aid organizations often failed to ____ people in affected communities about aid distribution and reconstruction.", "Opt_1": "elect", "Opt_2": "propose", "Opt_3": "indicate", "Opt_4": "consult", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest", "Opt_3_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It's no surprise that she is so quiet in class. She can ____ speak a word of English.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The police have not been able to establish a ____ for the brutal killing.", "Opt_1": "code", "Opt_2": "manner", "Opt_3": "motive", "Opt_4": "challenge", "Answer": "motive", "Opt_1_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_2_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "reason", "Opt_4_def": "difficult situation; problem"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government needs to find a better ____ for restricting the enormous amounts of money earned by top directors.", "Opt_1": "defeat", "Opt_2": "response", "Opt_3": "device", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "device", "Opt_1_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_2_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_3_def": "object; method", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government has increased the tax on petrol, ____ making itself very unpopular with motorists.", "Opt_1": "thus", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "respectively", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "so", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Vehicles that do not display a valid parking ____ will be towed immediately.", "Opt_1": "permit", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "underlie", "Opt_4": "block", "Answer": "permit", "Opt_1_def": "to allow", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_4_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "My father's contract in Germany will ____ at the end of the year.", "Opt_1": "supervise", "Opt_2": "improve", "Opt_3": "terminate", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The author had failed to annotate his report, so it was impossible to check the ____ of his claims.", "Opt_1": "truth", "Opt_2": "resource", "Opt_3": "figure", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_2_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_3_def": "number", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The class learns that Alzheimer's disease is a deterioration of cells within the brain that leads to ____ of memory.", "Opt_1": "amount", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "loss", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "loss", "Opt_1_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Insects are an important ____ of food in many societies throughout the world.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "background", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "source", "Answer": "source", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "where something begins, where you can find something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We could not detect any significant effect of our dietary recommendations in terms of birth weight and ____ of pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "duration", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In this report you must write a ____ of FIS and your previous school.", "Opt_1": "fallacy", "Opt_2": "comparison", "Opt_3": "authority", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "comparison", "Opt_1_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_3_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "My family can't ____ a new house. They're so expensive in Germany.", "Opt_1": "offend", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "afford", "Opt_4": "stipulate", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_4_def": "to require"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She is yet to ____ basic verb grammar. She often says He do .. instead of He does ...", "Opt_1": "prefer", "Opt_2": "degenerate", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to like better", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We would probably become engaged in discussions from which we could not extract ourselves and ____ our freedom of action would be limited.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "extremely", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "very"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The business tried to ____ its employees to work harder by offering an extra day's holiday to the best salesperson.", "Opt_1": "acknowledge", "Opt_2": "transform", "Opt_3": "cooperate", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The campus will be closed except for needed emergency services and ____ work.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "essential", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "reliable", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "by terrorists lies in the countries that possess such devices."}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If we accept your request to ____ the information, we will make reasonable efforts to inform others, including people you have authorized, of the ____ment.", "Opt_1": "label", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "claim", "Opt_4": "amend", "Answer": "amend", "Opt_1_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to change (usually to improve something)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "With her departure we have decided to ____ teaching Spanish this fall as we await the committee report.", "Opt_1": "refuse", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "suspend", "Opt_4": "attend", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_4_def": "to go to, to be present at"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is no ____ of an original idea in this essay.", "Opt_1": "trace", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "sum", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The former is preferable for a field of inquiry that is still in its infancy, whereas the latter is ____ for fields that have a developed theory.", "Opt_1": "equivalent", "Opt_2": "trivial", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "suitable", "Answer": "suitable", "Opt_1_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_2_def": "not important", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "good for a particular job or purpose"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I did not ____ the issue at the time. It was too big and I was not sure I would like the answer.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "remove", "Opt_3": "provide", "Opt_4": "exceed", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to take away", "Opt_3_def": "to give", "Opt_4_def": "to be more than or better than"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "For republicans since Cicero there can be no ____ without law, and no valid law or legal system when ____ is disregarded.", "Opt_1": "liberty", "Opt_2": "symptom", "Opt_3": "access", "Opt_4": "statistic", "Answer": "liberty", "Opt_1_def": "freedom", "Opt_2_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_3_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical number"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The more alert you are to the ____ words used and the explicit claims made in ads, the more aware you will become of your own use of words and ideas.", "Opt_1": "forthcoming", "Opt_2": "key", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "evident", "Answer": "key", "Opt_1_def": "coming soon", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "clear"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school decided to ____ when the angry parent said that he would contact his lawyer.", "Opt_1": "tend", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "spread", "Opt_4": "absorb", "Answer": "retreat", "Opt_1_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to take up"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Newspaper headline: MIT scientists devise a new way to ____ gene therapy.", "Opt_1": "deliver", "Opt_2": "address", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "suspend", "Answer": "deliver", "Opt_1_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_2_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government should ____ all its energy to reducing unemployment.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "organize", "Opt_3": "destroy", "Opt_4": "dedicate", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_3_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_4_def": "to devote (time and attention)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The main reason for not responding to terrorism was not an ____ issue, but an internal one: the government failed to fulfill its duties.", "Opt_1": "considerable", "Opt_2": "liable", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "external", "Answer": "external", "Opt_1_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_2_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "outside"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has no right to ____ what a woman should do with her body.", "Opt_1": "establish", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "interact", "Opt_4": "mention", "Answer": "dictate", "Opt_1_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_4_def": "to say; state"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There's no incentive to make an ____ if the teacher never gives you back your work.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "potential", "Opt_4": "target", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "good possibility", "Opt_4_def": "aim, goal"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Doctors ____ make mistakes which can have serious or even fatal consequences for their patients.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "fairly", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "quite, somewhat"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If he was ____ employed by the Grand Duke, that would account for his odd behaviour.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "indeed", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "When dealing with a real, ____ system such as a robot, however, this approach is simply not practical.", "Opt_1": "superior", "Opt_2": "annual", "Opt_3": "mental", "Opt_4": "physical", "Answer": "physical", "Opt_1_def": "better", "Opt_2_def": "yearly", "Opt_3_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_4_def": "of the body"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government was ____ successful in reducing teenage drinking during its first period in power.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The purpose of this study was to explore the internal and external factors influencing the ____ development of first generation Filipina Americans.", "Opt_1": "influence", "Opt_2": "staff", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "ratio", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He was a soldier, and doubtless felt that it was not his ____ to volunteer advice to the political department.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "layer", "Answer": "province", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "level"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I have a ____ idea why she has been absent, but I'm not sure.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "ultimate", "Opt_3": "previous", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "final or most important", "Opt_3_def": "the one before", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is my ____ intention to remain with my department for at least two years.", "Opt_1": "severe", "Opt_2": "average", "Opt_3": "firm", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "firm", "Opt_1_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_2_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_3_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Trying to water-ski for the first time is difficult but if you keep practising, you will ____ learn how to do it.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "eventually", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "in the end"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The first principle of this school is that all nationalities and cultures are equally important, even if some are more represented than others ____ the body of students.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Before having a major surgical ____ patients must always consent.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "detriment", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "province", "Answer": "procedure", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It was an extremely conservative institution, and did not ____ its business to any extent.", "Opt_1": "enlarge", "Opt_2": "procure", "Opt_3": "admit", "Opt_4": "suppress", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to make larger", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Roman Catholic Church along with the main Protestant denominations in Europe did not ____ the slave trade.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "submit", "Opt_3": "earn", "Opt_4": "suggest", "Answer": "oppose", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_3_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_4_def": "to say an idea; to recommend"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government has set up a programme to ____ refugees on entry to the country.", "Opt_1": "assist", "Opt_2": "compel", "Opt_3": "ignore", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "assist", "Opt_1_def": "to help", "Opt_2_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_3_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The cakes ____ of flour, sugar, eggs and milk.", "Opt_1": "convey", "Opt_2": "consist", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "depart", "Answer": "consist", "Opt_1_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to leave; to be different from"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "German Liberals had tried and failed to ____ Germany during the Revolution of 1848.", "Opt_1": "retire", "Opt_2": "unite", "Opt_3": "repeat", "Opt_4": "negotiate", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to stop working", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_4_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She will need an ____ performance to have any chance of winning the game. Her opponent is much better.", "Opt_1": "fundamental", "Opt_2": "medium", "Opt_3": "outstanding", "Opt_4": "pure", "Answer": "outstanding", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "in the middle", "Opt_3_def": "excellent", "Opt_4_def": "complete, 100%"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Her problems are close to the ____ and tend to be expressed in more direct, less symbolic, behavioral and emotional terms.", "Opt_1": "opportunity", "Opt_2": "penalty", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "trait", "Answer": "surface", "Opt_1_def": "chance", "Opt_2_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; aspect"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The partners realized that their small fund was not sufficient to support early ____ start-ups in the environment of the early 2000s.", "Opt_1": "stage", "Opt_2": "attention", "Opt_3": "duty", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "stage", "Opt_1_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_2_def": "focus", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "At the same time, we believe that the ____ over prejudice and hatred is achieved one person at a time.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "rank", "Answer": "victory", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It's always better to be ____ cautious and to protect yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "predominantly", "Opt_3": "indirectly", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_4_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions."}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is important that the government does not ____ significantly from what it promised during the elections.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "appreciate", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "depart", "Answer": "depart", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to leave; to be different from"}]]